<faq><target name="Involuntary Promotion"><entry source="Wave 4 FAQ" id="66">
      <question>What happens if the character I bring back from the KO area ends up with enough damage counters to KO it?</question>
      <answer>Both characters will end up KO’d, but the character that started in the KO area will be on the battlefield for a short time. For example, any ability that triggers when Upgrades are moved onto that character will still happen. If that character has any revenge abilities, those abilities will also happen.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-22" id="10-31">
      <question>
Involuntary Promotion: if I play it and chose a tapped character, does the revived character come back tapped or untapped?  
        </question>
      <answer>
Untapped.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-08" id="9-3">
      <question>
If I have a character with Bumpers attached, and I play Involuntary Promotion on a car in my KO area, does the returned character receive the Bumpers in time to prevent the damage counters from being moved?
        </question>
      <answer>
The damage and upgrades are moved at the same time. Bumpers’ effect won’t stop the damage counters from being moved.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-08" id="9-5" tags="Battle Master">
      <question>
Can I KO a Battle Master with Involuntary Promotion if I have no bots in my KO area?
        </question>
      <answer>
Yes. If you have no characters in KO or the characters in your KO area have too many stars, you can use Involuntary Promotion to KO one of your characters.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-08" id="9-6">
      <question>
Regarding Involuntary Promotion trigger timings, when I shift the upgrade and damage counters to the returned character. Do I get to choose to shift the damage counters first followed by the upgrades since they are both my triggers?
        </question>
      <answer>
No part of Involuntary Promotion is a triggered ability. The instructions are all followed in order and the damage counters and upgrades are moved at the same time.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-08" id="9-15">
      <question>
Does Involuntary Promotion count as "repairing" the resurrected character? In other words, could Torox or Ratchet benefit from its play?
        </question>
      <answer>
No. The character appears on the Battlefield fully repaired. It’s not repaired while on the Battlefield.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Aequitas Rules Roundup 2020-10-01" id="2" tags="Head Mode &amp; Body Mode">
            <question>
                Can you I Still Function a character with a Body mode?
            </question>
            <answer>
                
                You can't bring back a Body mode character from KO because it won't have a head. Effects like I Still Function! and Involuntary Promotion will not work at all to bring back a Body. You can, however, bring back a Head from KO because it will be in Bot mode (and only in Bot mode). 
            </answer>
        </entry>
    </target></faq>