<faq><target name="Heroism"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="86">
      <question>
    Let’s say the Upgraded character also has Heroism. If another character would take 5 or more attack damage, what happens?
</question>
      <answer>
    The damage that would be done to the defender is instead done to the character with Heroism and Force Field. That damage is still attack damage, so 4 damage is done to the Upgraded character instead.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="90">
      <question>
    What happens if I have more than one character with Heroism and attack damage would be done to a different character?
</question>
      <answer>
    You can choose which of the characters will take the damage.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="91">
      <question>
    Does the damage still count as attack damage?
</question>
      <answer>
    Yes. Any other card that cares about attack damage will still apply.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-10-25" id="8-8">
      <question>
I have a question concerning Heroism, the Wave 1 Utility. I have Heroism on a character and place the Take Cover! secret action during my turn. During my opponent's turn I reveal Take Cover!. When my opponent goes to attack and the attack damage is transferred to the character with Heroism what type of damage is this? Heroism is a tad vague on the damage that the character is taking. If its not attack damage I assume that Take Cover! could blank the attack effectively?
        </question>
      <answer>
Damage redirected by Heroism is still attack damage, so it is not affected by Take Cover.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-14" tags="Insecticon Skrapnel - Insecticon Leader">
      <question>
If I played Heroism on Insecticon Leader Skrapnel, would the redirected attack damage to Skrapnel still be reduced to 3?
</question>
      <answer>
Yes, redirected damage from Heroism is still attack damage.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-11" id="211-11" tags="Grimlock - Dinobot Leader,Metroplex - Autobot City,Scamper - City Patrol">
      <question>
So the board is 1 Grimlock on Player 1’s side and a Metroplex and Scamper on Player 2’s side. Player 1 attacks Metroplex since Scamper is untapped and unable to be targeted. Then Grimlock gets enough attack to kill both characters with skill since Metroplex is heavily damaged and Scamper has low defense and life. So, since the Grimlock attacked Metroplex while Scamper had Heroism, I assume that since Heroism only changes where the damage goes and not the actual attack that the damage a character takes through the effect of Heroism is effect damage and not battle damage. I want to know the ruling because if the damage IS battle damage then Grimlock’s skill does trigger and Player 2 loses, since Scamper would die as the rollover would kill Metroplex but if it is effect damage, then Grimlock’s skill wouldn't trigger and only Scamper would be KO’d.
      </question>
      <answer>
The damage redirected by Heroism is still attack damage. So Scamper would take enough to get KO’d and then Grimlock’s ability would trigger and the defender would have to assign the extra damage to Metroplex.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>