<faq><target name="Hunker Down"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="93">
      <question>
    What happens to characters who are in alt mode?
</question>
      <answer>
    Any character in alt mode, as well as characters who are in bot mode but whose alt mode isn’t a Tank, doesn’t flip. Then each Tank, whether it flipped or not, can get an Armor from your scrap pile.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="94">
      <question>
    If I have more Armors in my scrap pile than I have Tanks, what happens?
</question>
      <answer>
    You choose which Armor goes on which Tank. The same is true if you have more Tanks than you do scrapped Armors.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-4">
      <question>
Can I use Hunker Down to retrieve a Superior Plating from my scrap pile and play it on a bot (bypassing the Tech Research requirement)?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes. Hunker Down doesn’t ask you to play the card, so the requirement from Tech Research does not apply.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-08-23" id="4-8">
      <question>
Question about Unconventional Flying Object. Can this be played on a Spaceship that is already in bot mode in order to flip it to alt mode, essentially ignoring the first sentence as "already done" (somewhat similar to Hunker Down)?
        </question>
      <answer>
No, it cannot.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-22" id="10-24">
      <question>
Let's say I've got an Armor on one of my characters as well as Defensive Configuration, giving me an extra empty Armor slot. I then play Hunker Down which checks to see if I have an Armor or not. Since Configuration will be giving me an empty Armor slot, would I be able to put an Armor on my character through Hunker, or will it not work since I do still have an Armor in the 1st Armor slot?
        </question>
      <answer>
It will not work since your Tank already has an Armor attached.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-06-28" id="628-11">
      <question>
Does Leap of Faith get around requirement cards (Tech Research, Ancient Wisdom) like Hunker Down does? If I flip a superior equipment, can I play that without the Tech Research?
      </question>
      <answer>
Leap of Faith gives you the ability to play a card, but that card’s requirements must still be met. 
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-17" tags="Darkmount - Cruel Overlord">
      <question>
If I play Hunker Down and flip Darkmount to tank mode can I then choose to activate to Darkmount's ability to discard a card from my hand before equipping an armor?
</question>
      <answer>
No, you must finish resolving Hunker Down before any triggered abilities from character flips are resolved.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-22" id="422-1">
      <question>
If I play Hunker Down while Megatron - Living Weapon has a weapon in his armor slot, do I have to replace the weapon with an armor from my scrap pile, or can I choose not to?
      </question>
      <answer>
If you are able to, you must replace the weapon with an armor.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-22" id="322-4" tags="Demolisher - Devoted Decepticon,Megatron - Decepticon Leader">
      <question>
Regarding character triggers, the following scenario is Demolisher/Darkmount/Common Megatron all in bot mode. I play Brainstorm &gt; Hunker Down &gt; Rapid Conversion. Hunker Down flips all 3 to alt mode, then I play armors from the scrap pile if able. Once Hunker Down is complete, I play Rapid Conversion targeting Megatron to flip him into bot mode. Brainstorm is now resolved. Moving on to character triggers, would Demolisher’s ability now draw 1 or 2 cards? Would I be allowed to use Megatron’s flip ability? 
      </question>
      <answer>
In this scenario, Demolisher’s ability would draw 1 card and you would be able to use Megatron’s flip ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-26" id="426-4" tags="Jetfire - Air Guardian">
      <question>
Given Hunker Down, which says "Flip each of your characters from bot mode to tank mode. Then for each of your tanks that isn't upgraded with an Armor, put an Armor on it from your scrap pile", bypasses the requirement to play Tech Research for Superior Plating, does the same apply to Jetfire, whose wording is "When you flip to this mode - Put an Armor or Utility from your scrap pile onto this character"?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-18">
      <question>
I have a question: I have 3 tanks in bot mode and I play Hunker Down. I flip all of them to tank mode. Can I resolve their flip abilities first before the "Then" statement in Hunker Down where I search discard pile for armors?
      </question>
      <answer>
You must finish Hunker Down before using any flip abilities, which includes getting armor.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Aequitas Rules Roundup 2020-09-14" id="4">
            <question>
                Start Your Engines says "Flip each of your characters from bot mode to Car mode". Does this mean that you can target "Car mode" with Precision Fire? Is Car a mode?
            </question>
            <answer>
                No. Car is a trait and not a mode. Despite this card using 'Car mode', you should consider it as a short hand for 'a mode with the Car trait'. The same is true for Hunker Down's use of Tank mode, and Pop a Wheelie's use of Motorcycle mode.
            </answer>
        </entry>
    <entry source="Aequitas Rules Roundup 2020-09-14" id="15">
          <question>
            Does a card that refers to Bot Mode apply to a Titan Master (Head + Body mode)?
          </question>
          <answer>
            No. A character in Body mode is not also in Bot mode.

            This means that cards like Escape Route do not flip a Body mode character to Alt mode. For an example of a card that works with both Body mode and Bot mode characters, look at how Mission Briefing explicitly says 'in bot mode or body mode'. 
            Note that cards like Start Your Engines and Hunker Down do not flip the characters from Body mode to Alt mode, however if the characters have Car and Tank traits respectively, they still get the secondary effects of those cards. 
          </answer>
      </entry>
    </target></faq>