<faq><target name="Scrapper Gauntlets"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="110">
      <question>
    If one of my opponent’s characters has a Weapon, can I choose not to scrap it and draw a card?
</question>
      <answer>
    No. If there is an enemy Weapon, you must scrap it. You draw a card only if you can’t scrap an enemy Weapon.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-22" id="10-38">
      <question>
I have a character with a Reactive Armor. I play a Scrapper Gauntlets on that character. My opponent only has a single Armor in play.  What is the timing on the triggers here?  Are they considered simultaneous, or does one need to happen before the other?
        </question>
      <answer>
They trigger simultaneously and you resolve them in an order of your choosing.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-2" tags="Thrust - Supersonic Interceptor">
      <question>
If Thrust has a Grenade Launcher and boosts a character that is attacking, and the opponent reveals a Bolster, to play a Scrapper Gauntlets to scrap the Grenade Launcher, does Thrust donate 7 or 3 attack to the attacking character?
</question>
      <answer>
7 attack. The amount has already been locked in.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-22" id="322-8" tags="Wheeljack - Weapons Inventor">
      <question>
Wheeljack is in car mode is equipped with the following: 
Multi-Tool, Turbo Boosters, and Scrapper Gauntlets.
Bumblebee - Courageous Scout is tapped, in car mode, and equipped with the following:
Drill Arms, Crushing Size, and Multi Mission Gear.
For my action, I play Swap Parts between Wheeljack and Bumblebee. There are a LOT of abilities that fire off here and I'm curious to know, what would be the appropriate order? Most importantly, when does Wheeljack's ability take priority?
      </question>
      <answer>
These would all trigger at the same, so you would choose the order they happen in.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-19">
      <question>
If a character is equipped with 3 Combat Drones and the enemy plays a card such as Scrapper Gauntlets which scraps an enemy weapon, would just 1 of the 3 Combat Drones be scrapped or all 3? Thanks for all you guys do! Wave 2 is amazing!
      </question>
      <answer>
Just 1 and no, YOU’RE AMAZING.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>