<faq><target name="Start Your Engines"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="111">
      <question>
    What happens to characters who are in alt mode?
</question>
      <answer>
    Any character in alt mode, as well as characters who are in bot mode but whose alt mode isn’t a Car, doesn’t flip.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="112">
      <question>
    Does the Car I untap have to be one that just flipped?
</question>
      <answer>
    No. You can flip any of your Cars, even one that was already in alt mode and didn’t flip.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-09-20" id="6-2">
      <question>
I have 2 untapped cars and a Wave 2 Bumblebee tapped in bot mode. I play Ready for Action untapping him. I then flip him, triggering his mode ability and I play All-Out Attack allowing all my character to attack this turn as they are now all untapped prior me playing All-Out Attack (AOA). I put Anticipation Engine on one of my characters. I then attack with Bee first (tapping him), my 2nd character (tapping him), and finally the last character with Anticipation Engine (AE) which then taps him. AE triggers and I get Start Your Engines (SYE). I untap that last character with AE. Seeing how AOA was played during a time where all my characters were untapped, does that last character get to attack again since it was untapped with SYE post AOA being played?
        </question>
      <answer>
If the opponent has no untapped characters, you will attack again with the last character. If the opponent has at least one untapped character, you cannot attack again with the last character. All Out Attack allows one attack with each of your untapped characters at the time you play it.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-08-23" id="4-12">
      <question>
Does Start Your Engines affect cars in the KO area?
        </question>
      <answer>
No, it does not. Cards only affect cards in the KO Area if it is specifically stated in the card text.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-09-06" id="5-2">
      <question>
If I attack with a character that is upgraded with an anticipation engine and the first card flipped is an action that untaps my attacking character, such as Start Your Engines in a cars deck, does my character still count as attacking? Does it still flip battlecards for attack? Does my opponent need to wait for me to attack with the same, or another, character?

Another similar confluence of mechanics would be OPBL flipping a swap missions during attack and untapping. I know the effects and triggers are at slightly different points in the attack but the result is broadly the same; an attacker that hasn’t tapped out that round.
Is this intended?
        </question>
      <answer>
Changing the tapped/untapped status of a character does not affect whether it is attacking or not. At the end of that attack, if your opponent has any untapped characters, your turn ends. Otherwise, continue attacking with any of your untapped characters.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-09-06" id="5-10">
      <question>
Regarding All-Out Attack.
Scenario:

Bumblebee-TL tapped in bot mode, Prowl-MS and Cliffjumper-RW untapped in car mode.
I play All-Out Attack. Cliffjumper attacks and uses Anticipation Engine to trigger a Start Your Engines. Bee flips to car mode, Prowl is irrelevant, Cliffjumper untaps. Using Bee's extra action via flip to alt mode, I play Ready for Action to untap Bee. Cliffjumper finishes his attack. All 3 cars are now untapped.

Am I free to attack again with Cliffjumper?
Am I free to attack with Bee?
Am I free to end my attacks when I choose because of AoA?
        </question>
      <answer>
All-Out Attack says “Each of your untapped Transformers (Editor’s Note: Characters) can attack this turn.” At the time you play All-Out Attack, check which of your characters are untapped. Those characters are allowed to attack this turn, in sequence. They are not, however, required to attack. They can’t attack a second time unless your opponent is tapped out. As usual, you still must attack with at least one character during your turn if you are able.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Aequitas Rules Roundup 2020-09-14" id="4">
            <question>
                Start Your Engines says "Flip each of your characters from bot mode to Car mode". Does this mean that you can target "Car mode" with Precision Fire? Is Car a mode?
            </question>
            <answer>
                No. Car is a trait and not a mode. Despite this card using 'Car mode', you should consider it as a short hand for 'a mode with the Car trait'. The same is true for Hunker Down's use of Tank mode, and Pop a Wheelie's use of Motorcycle mode.
            </answer>
        </entry>
    <entry source="Aequitas Rules Roundup 2020-09-14" id="15">
          <question>
            Does a card that refers to Bot Mode apply to a Titan Master (Head + Body mode)?
          </question>
          <answer>
            No. A character in Body mode is not also in Bot mode.

            This means that cards like Escape Route do not flip a Body mode character to Alt mode. For an example of a card that works with both Body mode and Bot mode characters, look at how Mission Briefing explicitly says 'in bot mode or body mode'. 
            Note that cards like Start Your Engines and Hunker Down do not flip the characters from Body mode to Alt mode, however if the characters have Car and Tank traits respectively, they still get the secondary effects of those cards. 
          </answer>
      </entry>
    </target></faq>