<?xml version="1.0"?>
<faq name="Alpha Trion Protocols:Wave 3 FAQ" source_url="https://vectorsigma.info/alpha-trion-protocols" published_date="2021-03-01" sourced_at="2021-06-17">

    <target name="Banzaitron, Devious Orchestrator">
      <entry id="1">
        <question>
          Is Banzaitron a Leader if I have an Autobot head on a Decepticon body?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="2">
        <question>
          Is Banzaitron a Leader if I have him, a Decepticon, and a Mercenary on my starting team?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="3">
        <question>
          Does Banzaitron’s flip-to-Alt ability work with Hunker Down?
        </question>
        <answer>
          If you put an Armor on him with Hunker Down, and it doesn’t scrap before you have resolved his flip-to-Alt ability, you will get to do the effect because the “if Armor” clause isn’t until after the arrow.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Highbrow, Malware Brigadier">
      <entry id="4">
        <question>
          Can I return one of my own Upgrades to hand with Highbrow’s flip-to-Alt ability?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. Note this ability is not a “may” ability; you must do it if you flip.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="5">
        <question>
          What does “on your team” mean?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Presently on the battlefield under your control and not in the KO area-pulled from starting team.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="6">
        <question>
          Highbrow’s bot ability says “each character.” Does that work if I have two 9-stars with Highbrow in Bot mode?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Each of your 9-stars would get the +1 DEF in this case.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="7">
        <question>
          What happens when my highest star character gets KO’d?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The Bot mode ability is always checking, so the next highest star character or characters would now receive the bonus. If Highbrow is your character with the most stars, he will give himself the bonus.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Impactor, Unrelenting Veteran">
      <entry id="8">
        <question>
          If I use Hunker Down, do I get to use his Alt mode ability?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No. You have to be in his Alt mode at the start of your turn to have the option to use this ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="9">
        <question>
          Does his Bot mode ability apply to himself?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, as long as he is damaged.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="10">
        <question>
          Can I use the Alt mode ability even if no enemy characters have at least 10 damage on them?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, you can do the damage to one of your Wreckers, but you won’t damage any enemies if none of them meet the requirement for the “If you do” part of the ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Overlord, Sadistic Phase Sixer">
      <entry id="11">
        <question>
          Which KO area do you check for the Bot Mode ability?   
        </question>
        <answer>
          Both, a player’s references both players KO area
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="12">
        <question>
          What does it mean to be a Tank and Plane in Bot mode?   
        </question>
        <answer>
          It means that any cards that reference being in Plane or Tank mode are active in both of Overlord’s modes.  This means cards like Composite Armor can be put on him in either mode.  When you flip a Hull Down in either mode it is active, etc.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="13">
        <question>
          How does Hunker Down work with Overlord?  
        </question>
        <answer>
          If he is in Bot mode, you will flip him to Alt mode then complete the card
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="14">
        <question>
          Can I play upgrades or actions with Overlord’s attack ability?  
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, any card with exactly one star on it can be played, actions or upgrades.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Ransack, Hungry for Battle">
      <entry id="15">
        <question>
          Does Ransack’s first Alt ability count himself?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, he says *other* Insecticon on your starting team. If your team was 4 Insecticons, including him, your deck could have up to 3 extra stars in it.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="16">
        <question>
          Is Ransack’s flip-to-Alt ability optional; do I have to do it if I have an Upgrade I could scrap?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The ability is mandatory, if you have an Upgrade--so be careful about flipping this guy!
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="17">
        <question>
          Does Raider Brunt or Acid Storm stop Ransack’s Bot mode flipping of extra cards in battle?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, those characters care about Bold; this mechanic is similar to Bold, but is not the named mechanic unless keyworded as such.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Seaspray, Consummate Sailor">
      <entry id="18">
        <question>
          Does Seaspray’s first Alt ability count himself?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="19">
        <question>
          What does “on your team” mean?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Presently on the battlefield under your control and not in the KO area-pulled from starting team.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="20">
        <question>
          Seaspray’s bot ability says “each character.” Does that work if I have two 9-stars with Seaspray in Bot mode?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Each of your 9-stars would get the +1 ATK in this case.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="21">
        <question>
          What happens when my highest star character gets KO’d?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The Bot mode ability is always checking, so the next highest star character or characters would now receive the bonus. If Seaspray is your character with the most stars, he will give himself the bonus.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Slipstream, Spy-for-Hire">
      <entry id="22">
        <question>
          Can Slipstream’s flip-to-Alt ability give her the +1 ATK when it goes off?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="23">
        <question>
          What if my opponent has no cards in hand and I flip-to-Alt mode?   
        </question>
        <answer>
          Each of your Decepticons will get +1 attack as there is no card to discard with more than one icon, so the “Otherwise” ability will work the same as if you revealed a card with two or more pips to the ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Snapdragon, Ruthless Combatant">
      <entry id="24">
        <question>
          If my Snapdragon is in Alt mode, can I repair damage from Snapdragon?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, he only stops repair on other characters.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="25">
        <question>
          What happens if my Snapdragon is in Alt mode and my opponent plays Involuntary Promotion?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The character brought back from their KO will stay fully repaired because no damage can be moved to it, but the Upgrades from the original character will move as normal.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="26">
        <question>
          What happens if my Snapdragon is in Bot mode and I play System Reboot?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Both players scrap their whole hand. You draw 4 and scrap none; your opponent draws 4 and scraps 1 card because Snapdragon sees the act of drawing cards as one instance, regardless of number drawn.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="27">
        <question>
          What happens if my Snapdragon is in Bot mode my Opponent plays a Pep Talk to draw 2 after they draw their first card of the turn, do they scrap 2 cards or 1?
        </question>
        <answer>
          If your opponent has already drawn for turn, whether they draw 1 card with a card like Wedge Formation or 2 cards with a card like Pep Talk, they will only scrap 1 card from hand because of the “1 or more cards” clause.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="28">
        <question>
          If my Snapdragon KOs and enemy Battle Master, does his Bounty ability work so that I can choose to return that Battle Master to its owner’s hand/KO it from zone-changing?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, the game operates in all situations as attacking/active player’s abilities all happen, then defending/inactive player’s abilities all happen. Your Bounty trigger will resolve before your opponent’s Battle Master trigger will make them play it.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Starscream, Covetous Crony">
      <entry id="29">
        <question>
          When I flip him to Alt mode, and I reveal 3 Orange-pip cards, what happens?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Scrap each of them and give one of your Planes or Seekers Bold 1--three separate times.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="30">
        <question>
          When I flip him to Alt mode, and I reveal 3 blank-pip cards, what happens?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Add each of them to your hand and no characters get Bold 1 from this ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="31">
        <question>
          When I flip him to Alt mode, and I reveal 1 blank-pip card and 2 Blue-pip cards, what happens?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Add the blank to your hand, and scrap the other two. Then, give one of your Planes or Seekers Bold 1--two separate times.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="32">
        <question>
          When he’s in Bot mode, and a Seeker of mine attacks and flips 2 blank-pip cards, do I trigger the second ability twice or just once?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You only trigger it once because the condition is “at least one [blank-pip card].” It doesn’t matter if you flip 1 or 60 blank-pips; the ability will only trigger once on each attack.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Wheeljack, Outsider">
      <entry id="33">
        <question>
          If I started with him and 1 other Car on my team, but I flip the other Car to a mode where it doesn’t have that trait anymore, does he have Bold 2 now?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. Characters only have the traits of their active (read: face-up) side, and Wheeljack’s first Alt mode ability uses “while”, which means it is constantly checking to see your other characters’ traits.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="34">
        <question>
          When I use his flip-to-Alt ability, do I have to do one damage to one of my Wreckers?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, you do not. The “may” makes this an optional ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="35">
        <question>
          When I use his flip-to-Alt ability, can I do 1 damage to one of my Wreckers and NOT play the card?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, once you opt into doing the damage to one of your Wreckers, you MUST play the card scrapped to this ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Whirl, Lunatic Aerialist">
      <entry id="36">
        <question>
          What happens when I use his flip-to-Bot ability and reveal no Upgrades?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Add none of them to your hand and scrap all cards revealed this way. It hurts, but that’s how it works.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Fire And Fury">
      <entry id="37">
        <question>
          Can I play this with just Sparkstalker on my team and no other Firecons?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You can play this with just Sparkstalker or with one other Firecon or with two other Firecons. However many you have: that’s how many the second ability will apply to. The Stratagem is Common and uses Sparkstalker as its named character so that it is legal in the Junkion format, even if the rest of the Firecons aren’t.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="38">
        <question>
          Does the first line of text apply to my starting team or just my battle deck?
        </question>
        <answer>
          This does not apply to your starting team. “Your deck can…” is an ability only covering cards registered in your battle deck.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Unbreachable">
      <entry id="39">
        <question>
          Can I still play the Omega Supreme parts with Heroic Spotlight and Unbreachable?  
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, each Stratagem has its own conditions that playing all three constituent parts of Captain Omega Supreme together still satisfies, and the two Stratagems do not have the same named condition.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="40">
        <question>
          Can I play Unbreachable with only Omega Supreme (Base) without the other parts?  
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, you will just not have the ability to flip Unbreachable because you won’t be able to combine.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="41">
        <question>
          Once the Stratagem flips, will Capt. Omega Supreme still be Brave and Sturdy?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, just like characters, only the active (read: face-up) side of Stratagems is applied. Plus, that ability on the front side of Unbreachable specifically applies to a character with another name.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Armored Assault">
      <entry id="42">
        <question>
          What happens if I play an Armor after I play Armored Assault?   
        </question>
        <answer>
          Similar to Blade Flurry, it will not gain the Bold 1.  The bonus is determined when you play Armored Assault and won't change even if the character gains or loses an Armor later in the turn.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="43">
        <question>
          What if my Armor is scrapped before attacking or before flipping cards? 
        </question>
        <answer>
 You will keep the Bold 1 if somehow your armor is scrapped after you play Armored Assault.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="44">
        <question>
          Do the +2 and the Bold 1 have to go to the same character?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. The ‘it’ in the second line is applying to the character you chose for the first part of the ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Aura Of Dominance">
      <entry id="45">
        <question>
          Can I play this on a character with less than 11 stars?  
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, you will simply not gain the second ability. The character will still gain Bold 1, Tough 1 and 2 extra HP.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="46">
        <question>
          What happens if I play this on an 11*+ character and my opponent has a card disabling my cards from scrapping Upgrades on their characters?
        </question>
        <answer>
          They will still scrap a card from their hand, but will not have to scrap an Upgrade.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="47">
        <question>
          What happens if I play this on an 11*+ character and my opponent has a card disabling my cards from scrapping cards in their hand?
        </question>
        <answer>
          They would still scrap an Upgrade from one of their characters, but will not have to scrap a card from their hand.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Despite Any Difficulty">
      <entry id="48">
        <question>
          What happens if my opponent plays a Belligerence, I reveal DaD, and I flip a Matrix of Leadership and Master of Metallikato on defense?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Belligerence would turn this flip of normally [OU, (OUB)] to [OO, (OOB)], meaning that you only flipped 2 colors on defense--Orange and Black, regardless of your character’s tratis--and would thus get +2 DEF for that battle.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="49">
        <question>
          What happens if I flip 5 colors of pip during my defense flips?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Your character can only get up to +4 DEF, so it would receive that maximum: +4. Don’t forget that your Blue pips still apply to your defense total, though.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="50">
        <question>
          How long does this bonus last? Do I keep the +1-4 DEF all turn?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The bonus DEF only lasts during the battle in which you flipped those cards, and only for the first battle that character has after flipping DaD. If the character is attacked twice in one turn, but you revealed DaD on the first defense, you would only count cards flipped during that defense for the bonus, and that bonus fades before the second defense.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Dogfight">
      <entry id="51">
        <question>
          What happens if I play this with a Melee character on my team, but no Seekers?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You scrap an enemy Weapon, but move no damage.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="52">
        <question>
          What happens if I play this with a Seeker character on my team, but no Melee characters?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You move 1 damage from each of your Seekers to an enemy (scales for each character), but you would not scrap an enemy Weapon.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="53">
        <question>
          Do I get both effects if I have characters with both traits on my team?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes; this card doesn’t ask you to choose.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Harpoon Gun">
      <entry id="54">
        <question>
          Can I put this on Decepticons?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, just because it is an Autobot card doesn’t mean that restricts who you can play it on. Take Energon Mace as an inverse example.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="55">
        <question>
          What happens when I attack with this on a character who is a Leader, but isn’t a Wrecker?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You only get an additional +1, making the total added value of this card +2 ATK, Bold 1, Pierce 1.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="56">
        <question>
          What happens when I attack with this on a character who is a Wrecker, but isn’t a Leader?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You only get an additional +1, making the total added value of this card +2 ATK, Bold 1, Pierce 1.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="58">
        <question>
          Do I get both bonuses if I attack with a character who is both a Leader and a Wrecker?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="59">
        <question>
          Does my character keep the bonuses from the “attacks” triggers if my opponent reveals a Sabotaged Armaments?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You would keep the bonus ATK from the second and third abilities, if applicable. However, you would lose the Weapon’s static +1 ATK, Bold 1, and Pierce 1 that it normally gives.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Howling Howitzer">
      <entry id="60">
        <question>
          What happens if I flip this for battle with a non-Ranged character?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The hybrid pip would still count its color as an orange, but lacking the symbol trait in that pip will mean it has no battle effect for the battling character.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Never A Dull Moment">
      <entry id="61">
        <question>
          Can I play this card if I don’t have a Wrecker on my team?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="62">
        <question>
          Can I play this card if my opponent doesn’t have any Secret Actions in play?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="63">
        <question>
          When I play this card, do I have to do one damage to one of my Wreckers?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, you do not. The “may” makes this an optional ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="64">
        <question>
          When I play this card, can I do 1 damage to one of my Wreckers if my opponent doesn’t have a Secret Action in play?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="65">
        <question>
          When I play this card and I have a Specialist, do I have to make my opponent scrap a card?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. This ability isn’t optional.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="66">
        <question>
          Can my opponent scrap the Secret Action for the second ability that I returned to their hand with the first ability?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. Abilities on the card happen in order.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Outflank">
      <entry id="67">
        <question>
          Can I do damage to my opponent’s characters or only my own?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Much like Scouting Mission, you can choose any player’s character for this card.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="68">
        <question>
          What happens if I damage a non-Specialist character?
        </question>
        <answer>
          That character gets +2 ATK until end of turn and no cards are drawn.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="69">
        <question>
          What happens if I damage my opponent’s character and it is a Specialist?
        </question>
        <answer>
          That character will get +2 ATK until end of turn and your opponent will draw a card.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="70">
        <question>
          What happens if I choose an enemy Specialist that is wearing Holomatter Projector or Defense Driving or has Sturdy?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The ability on the card will only cause someone to draw if a Specialist is damaged this way. Cards or abilities preventing or reducing damage to 0 will not result in the character’s owner drawing a card.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Valiant Effort">
      <entry id="71">
        <question>
          If I have a Leader on my team, who can I give the +3 ATK to?
        </question>
        <answer>
          You can only give one of your Leader characters the +3 ATK. If you have multiple Leaders, you can choose between them to receive this bonus.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="72">
        <question>
          Can I play this card if I have no Leaders on my team?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. You would only get the second ability then, as long as you have a Ranged character.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="73">
        <question>
          Can I play this card if I have no Ranged characters on my team?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. You would only get the first ability then, as long as you have a Leader character.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="74">
        <question>
          If I have both a Leader and a Ranged character on my team, do I get both effects?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes. The card does not ask you to choose.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry id="75">
        <question>
          Can I play this card if I have neither a Leader, nor a Ranged character on my team?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, but it would do nothing.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
</faq>
