<?xml version="1.0"?>
<faq name="AP Wave 6:World|Strike FAQ" source_url="https://www.bayformers.net/faq/" published_date="2020-12-31" sourced_at="2021-06-19">
    <target name="Action Masters">
      <entry id="1">
        <answer>
          Action Master is a new character trait introduced in Wave BFA World|Strike. Most Action Masters cannot transform. Most begin in bot mode.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Allicons">
      <entry id="2">
        <answer>
          Allicon is a new character trait introduced in Wave BFA World|Strike.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Characters in multiple factions">
      <entry id="3">
        <answer>
          Characters like Optimus Prime, Dark Awakening belong to multiple factions at once – in Dark Awakening’s case, Autobot and Quintesson. They are not disallowed for the purposes of Spotlight Stratagems. For example, Decepticon Exhaust, Consumptive Condottiere is valid for either Villainous Spotlight or Enterprising Spotlight. Additionally, both Armada, Herald of Shrouds and Decepticon Exhaust would be able to use a Scoundrel’s Blaster.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Judges">
      <entry id="4">
        <answer>
          Judge is a new character trait introduced in Wave BFA World|Strike. Judges cannot transform. Judges begin the game in bot mode.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Sharkticons">
      <entry id="5">
        <answer>
          Sharkticon is a new character trait introduced in Wave BFA World|Strike.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Tentacle Upgrades">
      <entry id="6">
        <answer>
          Similar to Battle Master, Tentacle is a new Upgrade Trait introduced in Wave BFA World|Strike.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="All-Out Attack">
      <entry id="7">
        <answer>
          This errata was issued by the Aequitas rulings committee.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Angolmois Surge">
      <entry id="8">
        <answer>
          Unicron, Chaos Bringer is a character from the community-created Unicron Raid.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Are These Wires Important?">
      <entry id="9">
        <answer>
          As of this (FAQ's) writing, the only characters in the abilities box that are relevant to play either with cards in the official game or cards created by Team Bayformers are the following:
         <ul>
          <li>Beasts (introduced in Wave 4)</li>
          <li>Dinobots (Wave 1)</li>
          <li>Firecons (Wave 3)</li>
          <li>Trypticon (Wave 4)</li>
         </ul>
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Armed to the Teeth">
      <entry id="10">
        <answer>
          This card will also allow you to play in multiples Weapons that can fit into a single Weapons slot, including Tentacle Upgrades and Multi-Missile Pod.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Assuming Control">
      <entry id="12">
        <answer>
          As of this (FAQ's) writing, the only characters in the abilities box that exist either in cards in the official game or cards created by Team Bayformers are the following:
         <ul>
          <li>Judges (introduced in Wave BFA)</li>
          <li>Bombshell (Wave 1 and 2)</li>
          <li>Mindwipe (Wave 5)</li>
          <li>Soundwave (Wave 3 and Blaster vs. Soundwave)</li>
          <li>Trypticon (Wave 4)</li>
         </ul>
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="CNA-Encoded Armory">
      <entry id="13">
        <answer>
          As of this (FAQ's) writing, the only Upgrades that can be returned from the scrap pile via CNA-Encoded Armory are the following:
         <ul>
          <li>Body Armor</li>
          <li>Covert Armor</li>
          <li>Polydermal Graft (Wave BFA)</li>
          <li>Power Sword</li>
         </ul>
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Discordant Cacophony">
      <entry id="15">
        <answer>
          As of this (FAQ's) writing, the only characters in the abilities box that exist either in cards in the official game or cards created by Team Bayformers are the following:
         <ul>
          <li>Motorcycles (introduced in Wave 1)</li>
          <li>Blaster (Blaster vs. Soundwave)</li>
          <li>Frenzy (Blaster vs. Soundwave)</li>
          <li>Jazz (Wave 1)</li>
          <li>Soundblaster (Wave 4)</li>
          <li>Soundwave (Wave 3 and Blaster vs. Soundwave)</li>
         </ul>
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Forked Tentacle">
      <entry id="17">
        <answer>
          Using multiple Forked Tentacles does not allow you to select more than two separate choices from a list of abilities.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Loading the Cannon">
      <entry id="18">
        <answer>
          Play 3 Loading the Cannons in conjunction with Sergeant Kup, Veteran Sergeant and the Stratagem Death Crystal Cannon.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Premature Firing">
      <entry id="19">
        <answer>
          This pre-release battle card is not valid for play in current release versions. Future waves may reintroduce this card.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Shield Crash">
      <entry id="22">
        <answer>
          Shield Crash effectively swaps your chosen character’s Attack and Defense values at the moment of play. Events that modify those values after the moment of play (like flips) work as normal.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Squid Pro Quo">
      <entry id="23">
        <answer>
          For the Decepticon chosen for Squid Pro Quo, the bonus attack can stack due to counters placed on that Decepticon from other cards that turn.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="The Dweller Awakens">
      <entry id="24">
        <answer>
          This is revealed whenever the opponent plays an Action that would reveal or trigger any Secret Action in play. For example, if you have a face-down Infiltrate and a face-down The Dweller Awakens and the opponent plays a Peace Through Tyranny, you would flip both since the Peace Through Tyranny triggers Infiltrate.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="The Power to Bite">
      <entry id="25">
        <answer>
          This pre-release battle card is not valid for play in current release versions. Future waves may reintroduce this card.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Turnabout Snare">
      <entry id="27">
        <answer>
          At reveal, Turnabout Snare effectively swaps the attacker’s Attack and Defense values. Events that modify those values after reveal (like flips) work as normal.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="United Against Tyranny">
      <entry id="28">
        <answer>
          Press the Advantage is banned in many formats (including Bayformers-sponsored formats), but recent tournaments have shown its ability matches current card power levels post-Wave 5. United Against Tyranny is intended to be a PtA replacement that allows for PtA’s general card utility without PtA’s degenerate green battle icon.
          We recommend that formats that have both unbanned Press the Advantage and support Team Bayformers cards also ban United Against Tyranny, as it is intended to be a replacement for PtA.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Axor - Opportunistic Fencer">
      <entry id="29">
        <answer>
          When Axor, Opportunistic Fencer’s ability is activated for your Mercenary, the Bounty activated still belongs to the Mercenary and not to Axor. For example, Axor cannot repair 3 of his damage due to activating Detritus’s Bounty, though Detritus should repair 3 damage on Detritus.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Gilthor - Chained Amalgamation">
      <entry id="30">
        <answer>
          For his alt mode ability, the enemy is not required to take the damage in order to be flipped. For example, where the opponent’s Flamewar is Upgraded with a Holomatter Projector, it can still be flipped by your Gilthor, Chained Amalgamation when Gilthor is flipped to alt mode.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Mind Control Collar">
      <entry id="31">
        <answer>
          Its bot mode ability triggers KO effects normally, like Decepticon Quake’s.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Mind Control Helmet">
      <entry id="32">
        <answer>
          Its bot mode ability triggers KO effects normally, like Decepticon Quake’s.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Nacelle - Eager Aerospace Engineer">
      <entry id="33">
        <answer>
          As of this (FAQ's) writing, these are all the Decepticons that can benefit from his abilities.
         <ul>
          <li>Arcana</li>
          <li>Blackwing, Aerial Attacker</li>
          <li>Bombshell, Insecticon Mind-Controller</li>
          <li>Breakdown, Paranoid Scout</li>
          <li>Brisko</li>
          <li>Chasm</li>
          <li>Deadlock, Bounty Hunter</li>
          <li>Divebomb, Aerial Assault</li>
          <li>Grax</li>
          <li>Kreb</li>
          <li>Mixmaster, Materials Fabrication</li>
          <li>Monxo</li>
          <li>Predacon Headstrong, Ground Assault</li>
          <li>Raider Ion Storm, Infantry – Rainmaker</li>
          <li>Raider Nightstick, Ground Force – Weapons</li>
          <li>Raider Ravage, Espionage – Saboteur</li>
          <li>Raider Runabout, Infantry – Soldier</li>
          <li>Raider Runamuck, Infantry – Soldier</li>
          <li>Ramjet, Sky Smasher</li>
          <li>Ruckus, Combat Assault</li>
          <li>Starscream, Decepticon Lieutenant</li>
          <li>Thrust, Supersonic Interceptor</li>
         </ul>
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Optimus Prime - Dark Awakening">
      <entry id="34">
        <answer>
          In bot mode, Optimus Prime, Dark Awakening gains the benefits of his faction Upgrade ability as long as the faction Upgrades on him aren’t Autobot or Quintesson.
          As of this (FAQ's) writing, these are all the faction Upgrades that Optimus Prime, Dark Awakening can utilize to buff your team.
          Autobot:
         <ul>
             <li>Any Autobot Upgrade, though Noble’s Blaster also has a [G] pip</li>
         </ul>
          Decepticon:
         <ul>
          <li>Electro-Optical Visor</li>
          <li>Energon Mace</li>
          <li>Fusion Cannon of Megatron</li>
          <li>Hazardous Shield</li>
          <li>Null-Ray of Starscream</li>
         </ul>
          Mercenary:
         <ul>
          <li>Black Mail (Wave BFA)</li>
          <li>Dutch (Wave BFA)</li>
          <li>Subcontractor Agreement (Wave BFA)</li>
          <li>Valuable Contract</li>
         </ul>
          Quintesson:
         <ul>
          <li>Any valid Quintesson Upgrade</li>
         </ul>
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Tow-Line - Signals Engineer">
      <entry id="36">
        <answer>
          Tow-Line’s bot mode ability, when it qualifies on the battle flip, can return a face-up Secret Action or an Action you played during the turn in your hand after the battle.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Hit Me With That Beat">
      <entry id="39">
        <answer>
          Knowing the current amount of damage on Autobot Jazz, Special Ops is important to determine how much damage he takes when his alt mode ability triggers. For example, if he is at full health and an incoming attack triggers his alt mode ability, he first takes 1 point of damage, and then cannot take more than 1 damage for the attack. If he has 4 damage counters, first he takes 1 damage, and then cannot take more than 5 damage for the attack.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Orbital Command">
      <entry id="43">
        <answer>
          Your Orbital Command only grants the Guardian trait to the combined Captain Omega Supreme, Transport • City Defender, and not to each of his three individual components.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Pit of Judgement">
      <entry id="44">
        <answer>
          Your Judge must currently be on the battlefield (and not only in your KO area) in order to use Pit of Judgement to return KO’d Sharkticons to the battlefield. If you use I Still Function! or a similar effect to return a KO’d Judge to the battlefield, you may use Pit of Judgement to return a KO’d Sharkticon to the battlefield while the Judge is still on the battlefield. There are currently no methods to add swarm counters to Pit of Judgement beyond the initial starting team composition.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="The Solo Job">
      <entry id="48">
        <answer>
          You are required to have a single Mercenary amongst the members of your starting team. The Mercenary can be a dual-faction Mercenary, like Decepticon Exhaust.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Thermal Reciprocation">
      <entry id="50">
        <answer>
          The stat bonuses on Thermal Reciprocation affect all stat boxes in each mode of Autobot Powerglide, Haughty Show-Off. Therefore, with this Stratagem in play, Powerglide in alt mode has 3 Attack and 10 Health, Powerglide in bot mode has 4 Attack and 10 Health, and the S2 Thermal Reciprocator grants +3 Attack to an upgraded character.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Third Party Brigade">
      <entry id="52">
        <answer>
          Unlike when playing Recon System, when playing this Stratagem and attacking with your Combaticons, you do not flip an additional card after scrapping the first black pip card you flip. This is a designed drawback of playing this Stratagem.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="This Gun for Hire">
      <entry id="54">
        <answer>
          The stat bonuses on This Gun for Hire affect all stat boxes in each mode of Shockblast, Galactic Man. Therefore, with this Stratagem in play, Shockblast in alt mode has 4 Attack and 9 Health, Shockblast in bot mode has 3 Attack and 9 Health, and the Astro Magnum grants +3 Attack to an upgraded character.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="V2 Sonicsurge Drone Armor">
      <entry id="55">
        <answer>
          If your opponent attacks one of your characters when all of your characters are untapped and you tap your Raider Ravage, Espionage · Saboteur to boost their defense, Raider Ravage does not become the sole valid target for the opponent’s attack due to its tapping, as it is being tapped after the opponent has chosen a defender. See the Official Expanded Rules for further questions on the relevant attack timing.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Vehicle﹕ Off-Road Cycle">
      <entry id="57">
        <answer>
          This Stratagem primarily exists as a teaser for future new mechanics. The Vehicle descriptor does not currently grant any additional abilities beyond what is stated in the reminder text. When this is flipped, return a Sidecar Artillery from your scrap pile to your hand. This can only happen once per game.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
    <target name="Stim Shock">
      <entry id="58">
        <question>
          What happens to Stim Shock when the Bold has been reduced to zero, for example by Oppress?
        </question>
        <answer>
          If Stim Shock is revealed and an enemy character has had its Bold reduced to 0, it still has Bold. Stim Shock will still do 1 damage to it.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target>
</faq>
