<faq><target name="Snapdragon, Ruthless Combatant"><entry source="Alpha Trion Protocols:Wave 3 FAQ" id="24">
        <question>
          If my Snapdragon is in Alt mode, can I repair damage from Snapdragon?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Yes, he only stops repair on other characters.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Alpha Trion Protocols:Wave 3 FAQ" id="25">
        <question>
          What happens if my Snapdragon is in Alt mode and my opponent plays Involuntary Promotion?
        </question>
        <answer>
          The character brought back from their KO will stay fully repaired because no damage can be moved to it, but the Upgrades from the original character will move as normal.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Alpha Trion Protocols:Wave 3 FAQ" id="26">
        <question>
          What happens if my Snapdragon is in Bot mode and I play System Reboot?
        </question>
        <answer>
          Both players scrap their whole hand. You draw 4 and scrap none; your opponent draws 4 and scraps 1 card because Snapdragon sees the act of drawing cards as one instance, regardless of number drawn.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Alpha Trion Protocols:Wave 3 FAQ" id="27">
        <question>
          What happens if my Snapdragon is in Bot mode my Opponent plays a Pep Talk to draw 2 after they draw their first card of the turn, do they scrap 2 cards or 1?
        </question>
        <answer>
          If your opponent has already drawn for turn, whether they draw 1 card with a card like Wedge Formation or 2 cards with a card like Pep Talk, they will only scrap 1 card from hand because of the “1 or more cards” clause.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Alpha Trion Protocols:Wave 3 FAQ" id="28">
        <question>
          If my Snapdragon KOs and enemy Battle Master, does his Bounty ability work so that I can choose to return that Battle Master to its owner’s hand/KO it from zone-changing?
        </question>
        <answer>
          No, the game operates in all situations as attacking/active player’s abilities all happen, then defending/inactive player’s abilities all happen. Your Bounty trigger will resolve before your opponent’s Battle Master trigger will make them play it.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target></faq>