<faq><target name="Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops"><entry id="315-19">
      <question> 
Let's say I have Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops equipped with a Data Pad. When he attacks, would I trigger Data Pad's effect or Bombshell's skill first? Or do I get to choose the order they trigger in?
      </question>
      <answer>
You may choose the order because they are both attack triggers on your cards.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="1-3">
      <question>
I was playing with Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops with 5 health left, against Shockwave - Cybertron Commander. I scrapped 11 cards to KO him, but should his bot mode ability have triggered, killing me in the process?
</question>
      <answer>
Shockwave’s ability will trigger 11 times, but if those are the last two characters on the battlefield, your opponent will lose the game because Shockwave has been KO’d by Bombshell’s ability, but Bombshell is not yet KO’d by Shockwave’s ability.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="308-16">
      <question>
Based off of the ruling for Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication (bot mode) that states that if defender is KO'd due to Cosmos’ ability, no defense flips are performed, When Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops (bot mode) attacks, are there battle flips for either party if a KO occurs from a discard?
      </question>
      <answer>
Nope. That’d be a garden variety KO.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="211-6">
      <question>
Does Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops' effect trigger before or after battle cards are flipped for the attack?
      </question>
      <answer>
You choose to use his ability (or not) before cards are flipped by either player. If you do and the defending character is KO’d, nobody flips.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="211-7">
      <question>
If Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops uses its ability to KO an opponent's character card, does the battle end, or do you get to select a new target for an attack due to the original target no longer being active on your opponent’s side of the field?
      </question>
      <answer>
The battle ends. Bombshell is still swinging at the air where the defender used to be standing.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="228-10">
      <question>
If you attack with Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops in bot mode and the defender has the 1-star upgrade Recon System attached, is that +1 to the total number of cards to be scrapped by the attacker? No. Bombshell’s ability only counts stars from characters, not from battle cards.

Are you allowed to look at your opponent’s discard pile?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes. The discard pile and KO zones are areas of public information. Accurate information must be provided upon request during a game, but please be polite about it, and always ask permission before touching another player’s cards and handle them carefully.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>