<faq><target name="Bumblebee - Trusted Lieutenant"><entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="2">
          <question>Which promo cards are permitted in Constructed tournaments?</question>
          <answer>
              P1: Bumblebee - Electrum Warrior
              P2: Omega Supreme - Autobot Defense Base
              P3: Private Smashdown
              P4: Flamewar - Veteran Decepticon (Gold Foil Variant)
              P5: Bumblebee - Trusted Lieutenant (Gold Foil Variant)
              P6: Private Red Alert - Medic (Gold Foil Variant)
              P7: Nightbird - Enigmatic Agent
              P8: Raider Runamuck - Infantry Soldier (Gold Foil Variant)
              P9: Raider Runabout - Infantry Soldier (Gold Foil Variant)
              P10: Raider Road Hugger - Infantry Tactics (Gold Foil Variant)
              P11: All-Out Attack (Energon Edition Foil Variant)
              P12: Tandem Targeting System (Energon Edition Foil Variant)
          </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-6">
      <question>
We were having a debate at the local draft on when cards such as Bumblebee - Trusted Lieutenant says: When this attacks -&gt; You may scrap an Action from your hand. If you do, draw 2 cards. Our question is about flipping. Is tapping to attack put the flip cards on (basically all Transformers state: When this attacks/or defends -&gt; flip 2 battle cards) This isn’t stated specifically in the rules, but with cards like Dinobot Snarl allowing you to plan 2, you could very easily want to flip then place 2 defensive cards on top (or if you utilized Plan prior to the attack). We have all been playing it is before the flip, but since it isn’t stated anywhere that we could see officially, we’d love a clarification.
      </question>
      <answer>
Any ability that just says “When this attacks” and doesn’t look at what you flipped happens before you flip battle cards.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-01" id="401-5">
      <question>
Would playing multiple instances of Steamroll in the same turn allow for damage, if it were high enough to KO the second character as well as the initial character that was knocked out, to carry over to a second or third target? For example: Brainstorm into two Steamrolls or play Steamroll and then flip Bumblebee - Trusted Lieutenant into alt-mode and play a second or even a third Steamroll (if Brainstorm was played first). 
      </question>
      <answer>
Playing more than one instance of Steamroll on the same character has no additional effect. The extra damage will carry over only once.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-12">
      <question>
When you attack and scrap an action, what happens first: the draw two or the attack flip?
      </question>
      <answer>
If you’re referring to the Bumblebee - Trusted Lieutenant’s bot mode ability, you would draw two first. Attack abilities happen before flipping unless they’re related to the flip.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>