<faq><target name="Tournament Rules"><entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="25">
          <question>
              How do I get the official Tournament Rules?
          </question>
          <answer> 
              The Tournaments Rules may be downloaded from the <a href="https://wpn.wizards.com/en/document/transformers-tcg-tournament-rules">WPN Transformers TCG Tournament Rules</a> page.
          </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="15">
          <question>
              What is a Deck Check?
          </question>
          <answer> 
Deck checks may be performed at any tournament at the option of the head judge. A deck check compares the deck registration list to the current contents of a player’s deck. If they do not match, appropriate penalties may be issued.
          </answer>
      </entry>

      <entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="16">
          <question>
May I take notes?
          </question>
          <answer> 
Players are allowed to take written notes during a match and may refer to those notes while that match is in progress. At the beginning of a match, each player’s note sheet must be empty and must remain visible throughout the match. Players do not have to explain or reveal notes to other players. Judges may ask to see a player’s notes and/or request that the player explain their notes.
Players may not refer to other notes, including notes from previous matches, during games.
Between games, players may refer to a brief set of notes made before the match. They are not required to reveal these notes to their opponents. These notes must be removed from the play area before the beginning of the next game. Players taking excessive amounts of time reviewing notes may be subject to Slow Play penalties.
          </answer>
      </entry>

      <entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="17">
          <question>
              May I use an electronic device?
          </question>
          <answer> 
              Players may use electronic devices to do the following:

              <ul>
                  <li>Take and review notes (as outlined in section 2.11).</li>
                  <li>Briefly answer personal calls not related to the game.</li>
                  <li>Players may not use electronic devices to access outside strategic sources (websites, forums, etc.) or communicate with others in order to receive outside assistance. Players taking excessive amounts of time using an electronic device may be subject to Slow Play penalties.</li>
                  <li>Players wishing to view information privately on electronic devices during matches must request permission from a judge.</li>
                  <li>The Head Judge of an event may further restrict or forbid the use of electronic devices during matches.</li>
                  <li>Use of the Official Transformers TCG Companion App is permitted for damage/health tracking.</li>
              </ul>
          </answer>
      </entry>

      <entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="24">
          <question>
How many players are required for a tournament to remain Officially Sanctioned?
          </question>
          <answer> 
Sanctioned Transformers TCG tournaments require a minimum of four (4) players, and a minimum of two rounds must be played. 
          </answer>
      </entry>

  <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="14">
        <question>
            If I start with Overkill on my team, can I put an Overkill from outside the game into my KO area?
        </question>
        <answer>
            No, this will be more covered in a Tournament Rules Doc. You may only ever have one of each named character on your battlefield or in the KO area. This concept is further emphasized by the word “different” among the many abilities in this same vein.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target></faq>