<faq><target name="Major Ultra Magnus - Infantry - City Commander"><entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="148" mode="alt">
      <question>When do I use this ability?</question>
      <answer>You use it before the game begins. You’ll put Ultra Magnus Armor onto Major Ultra Magnus, then shuffle the rest of your deck and draw 3 cards for your opening hand.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-17" id="517-1" tags="Major Ultra Magnus - Infantry - City Commander,Private Firedrive - Ground Command - Artillery">
      <question>
Let's say I have Major Ultra Magnus in bot mode and Private Firedrive on the field, with Firedrive having 1 health remaining. If I attack with Ultra Magnus and trigger his bot mode ability, which causes Firedrive to die and I put the Duo-Charge Electrostatic Photon Cannon onto Ultra Magnus, what happens? Does Ultra Magnus get the +3 attack for this battle? Am I able to scrap cards from my hand to increase said attack?
      </question>
      <answer>
Major Ultra Magnus will get the +3 attack, but since the long-name weapon was attached after he began his attack, the ability will not trigger and you will not be able to scrap any cards to add to your attack.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-17" id="517-6" tags="Major Ultra Magnus - Infantry - City Commander,Nemesis Prime - Dark Clone">
      <question>
If I have Major Ultra Magnus with 16 Damage on him and my opponent has Nemesis Prime with 15 Damage on him and I Attack Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend, causing my bot mode skill to trigger, does this cause Major Ultra Magnus to be KO’d and Nemesis Prime to be KO’d therefore no combat with Optimus?
      </question>
      <answer>
That is correct.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-26" id="426-10" tags="Specialist Ratchet - Engineering - Rescue &amp; Repair,Private Trailbreaker - Infantry - Fortification &amp; Defense,Major Ultra Magnus - Infantry - City Commander">
      <question>
For Wave 3 Ratchet, Ultra Magnus, Trailbreaker and Wheeljack. Do you search for their related card before you draw starting hand or after?
      </question>
      <answer>
Before the game starts, find their related card, shuffle, then draw three cards for your opening hand.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>