<faq><target name="Drift - Noble Warrior"><entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="7">
        <question>
            Why does he deal himself a damage at the start of the game instead of starting with 1 less HP?
        </question>
        <answer>
            We elected to give him the ability to do damage to himself for 2 core reasons. The first being a nod to the “lore” aspect of the character. The second being the potential of expanded future design space. Characters starting with damage on them open up many Battle card interactions.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="8">
        <question>
            My opponent has a Fangry with Parsec; does Drift have Stealth from him in alt mode?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes, Fangry may have the Autobot Tag, but is still a Decepticon and Drift’s Ability will grant him Stealth against him. This is in line with the WotC ruling of inclusivity of Faction;having “Stealth against Decepticons” might as well read “Stealth against Decepticons+”.  If there were ever a situation in the future where a dual-faction Decepticon-Mercenary was available to your opponent, Drift would have Stealth from that character, as well.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="9">
        <question>
            My opponent has a Perceptor with Grax; does Drift have Stealth from him in alt mode?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Perceptor may have the Autobot Tag but is still a Decepticon because of the Grax head.  Thus, Drift’s Ability will grant him Stealth in this scenario.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="10">
        <question>
            Can I flip Drift to alt mode and not do him 2 damage?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes, you only need to do the damage if you choose to use the ability.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="11">
        <question>
            My opponent has a tapped character and an untapped Fangry with Parsec; if I flip Drift to bot mode and deal him 2, can I attack the Fangry/Parsec?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="12">
        <question>
            My opponent has a tapped character and an untapped Perceptor with Grax; if I flip Drift to bot mode and deal him 2, can I attack the Perceptor /Grax?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="13">
        <question>
            If my opponent has a tapped character with Brave and I flip Drift to bot mode and do 2 to him, can I attack one of my opponent’s untapped characters and ignore the Brave guy?
        </question>
        <answer>
            No, since the target with Brave is still a legal target for Drift to attack, even after the ability (you are not forced to attack an untapped character after all), the Brave forces you to attack that character as long as it is among the possible characters available to select in combat.  Since Drift’s bot mode ability essentially adds your opponent’s untapped Decepticons to the normal list of characters available for him to attack, the Brave would still apply.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target></faq>