<faq><target name="Autobot Jazz - Special Ops"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="24" mode="alt">
      <question>
    If the attacking character would deal more than 2 damage, what happens to the extra damage?
</question>
      <answer>
    The extra damage doesn’t happen. The attacking character will deal only 2 damage.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="25" mode="alt">
      <question>
    Let’s say Autobot Jazz defends and the attacker has an ability that deals damage to him. Does that
damage count for Autobot Jazz’s ability?
</question>
      <answer>
    Yes. Any damage dealt to Autobot Jazz while he’s defending and his ability is active will count. If the
attacker has an ability that deals 1 damage to Autobot Jazz, then he can’t take more than 1 more
damage from the attack.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-28" tags="Autobot Jazz - Special Ops">
      <question>
Jazz in Alt Mode is defending against Megatron - Decepticon Leader in Bot Mode. They flip no extra oranges on attack, and I flip 4 white on defense. Does Jazz then take 3 (because of the Pierce 3 minimum) or 4 (because the Pierce completely nullifies the ability)?
      </question>
      <answer>
4. Pierce completely nullifies Jazz’s ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-32" tags="Autobot Jazz - Special Ops">
      <question>
What checks first when you have a Force Field on Jazz in Alt Mode? Would Jazz's ability reduce his damage to 2, or would Force Field reduce to it 4 and then Jazz's ability would reduce to 2 if he flips white pips?
      </question>
      <answer>
Jazz’s ability would keep him from ever taking more than 2 damage, so Force Field would not trigger.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-06-07" id="607-17" tags="Pierce,Autobot Jazz - Special Ops">
      <question>
If a character’s pierce is reduced to zero pierce would it still be considered pierce? More specifically, since the opposing character is attacking with pierce, but it’s reduced to zero, would Jazz’s ability trigger, allowing only two damage to hit?
      </question>
      <answer>
A character with Pierce, whose Pierce score is reduced to 0 or less still has Pierce.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-40" tags="Autobot Jazz - Special Ops">
      <question>
If I have Jazz equipped with Point Defense System while defending against an enemy with exactly 2 pierce after combat flips, will this enable Jazz's ability to trigger if I flipped 2 white icons?
</question>
      <answer>
No. Point Defense System doesn’t cause a character to gain or lose pierce. The attacking character with pierce 2 will have its pierce reduced to 0, but it still has pierce. RIP Jazz.
</answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>