<faq><target name="Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="21" mode="bot">
      <question>
        If there are two cards left in my deck, and I attack with Autobot Cosmos, will his ability trigger?
    </question>
      <answer>
        Yes. You reshuffle your scrap pile into your deck as soon as the deck is empty. In this case, Autobot Cosmos will attack, you’ll flip up the two remaining cards in your deck, and the defender will be KO’d (assuming it has 12 starsor fewer). Your opponent won’t flip any battle cards for the attack if their character is KO’d this way.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="22" mode="bot">
      <question>
        Say Autobot Cosmos has a Data Pad. Will Autobot Cosmos’s ability trigger if you draw the last card of your deck while he’s attacking?
    </question>
      <answer>
        Yes. Drawing the last card of your deck will cause you to shuffle your deck, and this will cause Autobot Cosmos to KO the defender.
    </answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-14" tags="Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication">
      <question>
When I attack with Cosmos in bot mode and then Anticipation Engine activates and I flip Rapid Conversion and flip him to alt mode. Would his KO effect take place since he’s no longer in bot mode? And I no longer have cards in my deck?
</question>
      <answer>
If during Cosmos’ attack, Anticipation Engine reveals Rapid Conversion as the last card in your deck, and you play it, you will immediately shuffle your deck, triggering Cosmos’ ability, then flip Cosmos to Alt Mode.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-17" tags="Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication">
      <question>
Say I have 21 cards in hand, I flip Autobot Cosmos and scrap my entire hand and then draw the same amount. If I only have 6 cards in my deck, do I draw the 6 cards, reshuffle because I had already scrapped my hand and then draw out 15 more?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-28" id="528-12" tags="Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication">
      <question>
I attack with Autobot Cosmos in bot form and have 2 cards left in my deck, they are both orange. Do I shuffle the deck because there are zero cards, or do I reshuffle on my opponent's turn when I am forced to draw?
      </question>
      <answer>
You shuffle your deck as soon as there are no cards left.
      </answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-22" id="10-36" tags="Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication,Lord Megatron - Conqueror of Cybertron">
      <question>
Autobot Cosmos is in Bot mode and attacks Lord Megatron in Bot mode. During Cosmos’ attack against Lord Megatron, I have to reshuffle. Does the reshuffle trigger both Cosmos and Lord Megatron's abilities at the same time? Or does Cosmos KO Lord Megatron first?
        </question>
      <answer>
Cosmos would KO Lord Megatron first. Megatron’s ability will still happen afterwards if the game has not ended.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-16">
      <question>
Based off of the ruling for Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication (bot mode) that states that if defender is KO'd due to Cosmos’ ability, no defense flips are performed, When Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops (bot mode) attacks, are there battle flips for either party if a KO occurs from a discard?
      </question>
      <answer>
Nope. That’d be a garden variety KO.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>