<faq><target name="Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="32" mode="alt">
          <question>
    If I scrap three Upgrades from Chop Shop, can I repair 1 damage from each of three of my
Insecticons, or do I have to repair 3 damage from one Insecticon?
</question>
<answer>
    You can choose a different Insecticon for each repair.
</answer>
</entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="33" mode="bot">
      <question>
    If Chop Shop has a Weapon attached to him, can you move another Weapon onto him?
</question>
      <answer>
    Yes, but you’ll have to scrap the Weapon he originally had.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="34" mode="bot">
      <question>
    If the Upgrade I move onto Chop Shop has an ability that triggers "when the Upgraded character
attacks," does that ability trigger?
</question>
      <answer>
    No. That Upgrade wasn’t on Chop Shop when he attacked, so that ability won’t trigger.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="35" mode="bot">
      <question>
    If the Upgrade I move onto Chop Shop gives him Bold or an ability to flip extra battle cards when
attacking, do I flip extra battle cards?
</question>
      <answer>
    Yes. Chop Shop’s ability happens before you flip battle cards, so Upgrades that give Chop Shop Bold
will work.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="36" mode="bot">
      <question>
    Can Chop Shop’s ability be used to move an Upgrade that says "Put only on Planes" onto him?
</question>
      <answer>
    No. Any ability that says what an Upgrade can be put on still apply, so you can’t sneak Upgrades onto
Chop Shop that he can’t have.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-09-20" id="6-7" tags="Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon,Thrust - Supersonic Interceptor">
      <question>
Please clarify the interaction between Thrust and Chop Shop under the following scenario:
    Chop Shop flips to bot-mode
    Equip a Grenade Launcher onto Thrust
    Chop Shop attacks
    Thrust and Chop Shop's abilities trigger at the same time, so order of resolution is up to the turn-player
    1) Resolve Thrust's ability and tap him to add 7 atk (base + Grenade Launcher) to Chop Shop
    2) Resolve Chop Shop's ability moving the Grenade Launcher from Thrust to Chop Shop
    Chop Shop's final attack is [BASE] + [GRENADE_LAUNCHER] + [THRUST_BASE] + [GRENADE_LAUNCHER]; 4 + 4 + 3 + 4 = 15
    Battle flips omitted
Is this correct?
        </question>
      <answer>
You can choose to resolve Thrust and Chop Shop’s abilities in this order. You could also choose to resolve them in the other order, but that would probably not turn out as well for you, so maybe don’t.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-8" tags="Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon">
      <question>
If Chop Shop in bot mode attacks and moves a Grenade Launcher from another character to him, those the Grenade Launcher sack itself?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-9" tags="Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon">
      <question>
If Chop Shop in bot mode attacks, and moves a Bashing Shield from another character to him, does the effect of Bashing Shield activate?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-01" id="201-5" tags="Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon">
      <question>
At what point does the upgrade I chose to move to Chop Shop take effect? During the attack so I gain the possible effect for my current attack, or does the cards effect (additional attack, additional bold, etc.) not happen until the next time I attack with Chop Shop?
      </question>
      <answer>
You would get the benefits of the upgrade immediately, with the exception of abilities that trigger from Chop Shop attacking, because that event would have already passed (i.e. Data Pad).
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-14" tags="Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon">
      <question>
Can Chop Shop (Bot Mode) take upgrades that normally couldn't be equipped to him?
      </question>
      <answer>
No. You must be able to put said upgrades on Chop Shop legally.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-15" tags="Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon">
      <question>
Do effects on upgrades that trigger "when equipped" activate if Chop Shop (Bot Mode) takes them?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Aequitas Rules Roundup 2020-10-01" id="13" tags="Toolbox,Chop Shop - Sneaky Insecticon,Raider Ratbat - Spy Patrol - Fuel Scout">
            <question>
                How does Vesatility interact with Toolbox? Would it effectively double the impact of Versatility, since each battle icon colour you flip is a separate instance, or does it just add 1 to the total being repaired?
            </question>
            <answer>
                Toolbox only adds 1 to the total being repaired. The 'for each' in Versatility is looping to calculate the amount of repair that will be done, then the repair is applied as one event. Raider Ratbat works the same way.
                Wave 1's Chop Shop however works the other way. It has the repair inside the for each, allowing Toolbox to apply for each repaired damage. 
            </answer>
        </entry>
    </target></faq>