<faq><target name="Megatron - Decepticon Leader"><entry id="315-13">
      <question>
Megatron - Decepticon Leader in bot mode has a total of Pierce 6 due to his ability and the upgrade equipped (Crushing Threads) and attacks with a total of 5 regular attack damage. Prowl has (Force Field) equipped and defends for a total of 2 because no blue pips were revealed. Force Field does not trigger because the attack damage did not exceed the 5 and higher damage limit. Is this right? Does he take 3 regular damage or 6 pierce damage?
      </question>
      <answer>
Because Megatron has Pierce 6, he would do 5 attack damage (remember that attack damage can’t be higher than the character’s attack, even with pierce). This causes the Force Field to trigger, so instead, he’ll do 4 damage and the Force Field will be scrapped.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="RR1-21" tags="Pierce,Megatron - Decepticon Leader">
      <question>
Common Megatron is in Bot mode. He has Grenade Launcher equipped giving him +4 attack. He attacks Barrage in Bot mode. Megatron does not flip any orange icons and Barrage does not flip any blue icons. Megatron's attack is 8 w/Pierce 3 (due to his ability), while Barrage has 2 defense. Does he only deal 6 damage for the entire attack or 3 only due to his Pierce 3?
      </question>
      <answer>
6. Pierce is a minimum damage.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="218-28" tags="Autobot Jazz - Special Ops">
      <question>
Jazz in Alt Mode is defending against Megatron - Decepticon Leader in Bot Mode. They flip no extra oranges on attack, and I flip 4 white on defense. Does Jazz then take 3 (because of the Pierce 3 minimum) or 4 (because the Pierce completely nullifies the ability)?
      </question>
      <answer>
4. Pierce completely nullifies Jazz’s ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="322-4" tags="Demolisher - Devoted Decepticon,Megatron - Decepticon Leader">
      <question>
Regarding character triggers, the following scenario is Demolisher/Darkmount/Common Megatron all in bot mode. I play Brainstorm &gt; Hunker Down &gt; Rapid Conversion. Hunker Down flips all 3 to alt mode, then I play armors from the scrap pile if able. Once Hunker Down is complete, I play Rapid Conversion targeting Megatron to flip him into bot mode. Brainstorm is now resolved. Moving on to character triggers, would Demolisher’s ability now draw 1 or 2 cards? Would I be allowed to use Megatron’s flip ability? 
      </question>
      <answer>
In this scenario, Demolisher’s ability would draw 1 card and you would be able to use Megatron’s flip ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>