<faq><target name="Thundercracker - Mach Warrior"><entry source="Wave 1 FAQ" id="69" mode="alt">
      <question>
    What happens if my opponent doesn’t have any melee enemies?
</question>
      <answer>
    In that case, nothing happens.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-14" tags="Thundercracker - Mach Warrior,Autobot Hound - Long-Range Scout">
      <question>
Had an interesting situation occur last night. Had Thundercracker on defense with 4 health remaining equipped with a Crash Landing. Autobot Hound was attacking who only had 2 health remaining. Hound had enough attack power after flipping to take out Thundercracker. Both were the last bots on each side, would Crash Landing still go off, creating a Draw?
      </question>
      <answer>
Hound will KO Thundercracker and win the game before Thundercracker can Crash Land and KO Hound.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-26" id="426-14">
      <question>
Does Thundercracker - Mach Warrior get +1 attack if you play a Secret Action?
      </question>
      <answer>
That’s a big 10-4.
      </answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-12" tags="Thundercracker - Mach Warrior">
      <question>
Do character abilities still trigger if the requirements are met through cards played but negated by the opponent or otherwise?
For example, Wave 1 Thundercracker’s bot mode ability --&gt; Player 1 uses Supercharge, but player 2 reveals Infiltrate and negates Supercharge. Does Thundercracker's ability still trigger because an action was played? Meaning he would indeed get +1?
</question>
      <answer>
The Infiltrate will scrap the action you played and negate its effect, but Thundercracker’s ability still triggers because you played an action.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-48" tags="Thundercracker - Mach Warrior">
      <question>
How does Brainstorm work, exactly? Do I play the two actions from my hand immediately, then resolve them, or do I resolve the first action before playing and resolving the second action? What if a character's trigger happens between actions, such as Wave 1 Thundercracker? Are triggers resolved before or after the action that triggers them?
</question>
      <answer>
You play one action from your hand, then you play the second, then resolve the triggers caused by those actions.
</answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>