<faq><target name="Combat Commands"><entry id="66">
      <question>If I have a Sentinel in my KO area that’s in alt mode, can I flip it to bot mode?</question>
      <answer>No. Combat Commands works only on Sentinels in your KO area in alt mode.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry id="510-1">
      <question> 
I have a ruling question on Insecticon Skrapnel - Insecticon leader. If my opponent attaches Combat Commands onto Ironhide - Steadfast Brawler and declares an attack into Skrapnel while Skrapnel is in bot mode, and uses Combat Commands’ effect to flip Autobot Hot Rod - Impulsive fighter and deal 1 damage to Skrapnel, do I only take 2 damage from the attack since Skrapnel is defending and any damage dealt to him while defending counts towards his skill based off of the FAQ in the Transformers official app? 
      </question>
      <answer>
Apologies for the confusion here. We ruled this differently, but the FAQ was apparently not updated to reflect that. Here’s how that question should read:
“Q: Let’s say Insecticon Skrapnel defends and the attacker has an ability that deals damage to him. Does that damage count for Insecticon Skrapnel’s ability? 
A: No, only attack damage counts towards Skrapnel’s ability. Damage dealt by other abilities won’t count, even if it happens during an attack.”
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="607-18" tags="Prowl - Strategic Mastermind,Autobot Mirage - Counterintelligence">
      <question>
What happens when the Sentinel Prowl attacks with Combat Commands and I want to use it on Mirage, into a character equipped to with Security Console? Does turn player flip flop Mirage first to look for an action to scrap before they draw?
      </question>
      <answer>
The attack causes two abilities to trigger. One is yours (Combat Commands) and the other is your opponent’s (Security Console). You do yours first, but this causes another of your abilities to trigger (Mirage). You continue to use your abilities until you have none, then your opponent can use any of their pending abilities in any order. In this scenario, you would first use Combat Commands’ ability, then use Mirage’s ability, then your opponent would use Security Console’s ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="607-19">
      <question>
Let's say I'm playing Sentinels and I have Ironhide - Steadfast Brawler in my KO area in Alt mode. I flip him to Bot mode, giving my characters Pierce 2 until the end of the turn. If I then put a Combat Commands onto one of my Bots in play, let's say Prowl - Strategic Mastermind, attack with him, and use Combat Commands to Trigger Ironhide's KO ability, do my characters get pierce 4 until the end of turn, or does it stay at pierce 2? 
      </question>
      <answer>
Each character’s ability is separate and stacks, so in this scenario you would end up with Pierce 4.
      </answer>
    </entry>
  </target></faq>