<faq><target name="Decepticon Crown"><entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="52" mode="bot">
      <question>What happens if I flip more than one Decepticon Crown in the same battle?</question>
      <answer>Starscream—sorry—King Starscream—’s ability will trigger once for each Decepticon Crown you flip. Hit 2 of them and get +6 to your attack and defense for the turn.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-09-06" id="5-5" tags="Specialist Flamewar - Special Ops - Hunter">
      <question>
Since it sounds like (understandably) that a comprehensive rules document might take a while, perhaps you could answer a more specific timing question then.

Taken to a corner case, how would a player properly process an attack in the following scenario.

Your team:

Specialist Flamewar in bot mode equipped with an Anticipation Engine in her weapon slot, a Metal Detector in her Utility slot. She has Focus 2 from her bot mode ability.

Her teammate, Raider Aimless has a Decepticon Crown equipped in his Utility slot giving out Plan 1 when a Decepticon attacks.

Her other teammate General Optimus Prime is in Alt Mode giving Bold 1 and Tough 1 to his teammates.

What would be the proper sequence of triggers when Specialist Flamewar initiates an attack? Which goes first Plan, Focus, the Equipment Triggers? Which Equipment Triggers first? Can both trigger on the same combat if you have an equipment and an action (or vice versa) as your top 2 cards?
        </question>
      <answer>
When Specialist Flamewar attacks, the abilities of Anticipation Engine, Metal Detector, and Decepticon Crown will all trigger. As the attacking player, you will resolve all of those abilities in the order of your choosing, one at a time. Then you will use your Focus ability. Then, you will flip battle cards, including an extra from General Optimus’ Bold 1.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-9">
      <question>
I attack with Starscream - Decepticon King in Bot mode, who is equipped with Recon System. I flip battle cards and flip a Decepticon Crown. If I use Recon System to scrap Decepticon Crown, does Starscream still get its effect since Decepticon Crown was flipped, despite it being scrapped later?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-26" id="426-3" tags="Major Shockwave - Applied Sciences - Scientist">
      <question>
My question is regarding the new Major Shockwave. In its ability when it states “Decepticon cards,” what does that mean exactly? I know certain cards like Decepticon Crown and Swindled have Decepticon-specific effects and have purple coloring in their titles. Are those the types of cards that could be used with new Shockwave’s ability?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-18">
      <question>
If I attack with Starscream - Decepticon King in bot mode and flip multiple Decepticon Crowns, does his effect trigger multiple times on the same attack?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes. Starscream gets his bonus for each crown flipped. It is the most Starscream of all Starscream moves.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Aequitas Rules Roundup Allied Crossplay 2022-09-15" id="27">
        <question>
            When can I stop an attacking character's ability from triggering by removing a necessary flipped battle card?
        </question>
        <answer>
            When the ability reads similar to "When this attacks and flips [Card-Condition]", removing the right card would permit you to block the attackers ability. That is because this language reviews the cards flipped after they have all been flipped, including the two extra for a white icon. For example Metroplex's bot mode ability. However when it reads "When you flip [Single-Card-Condition] while this is attacking", the ability would trigger before you had the opportunity to remove the card. This is because this language triggers on a single card flip event. An example is Starscream - Decepticon King flipping a Decepticon Crown.
        </answer>
      </entry>
    </target></faq>