<faq><target name="Energized Field"><entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="75">
      <question>If I flip two orange battle icons, does it deal 2 damage?</question>
      <answer>No. The ability does a maximum of 1 damage, no matter how many orange battle icons you flip.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Wave 4 FAQ" id="72">
      <question>If Overheat is revealed, do effects like Energized Field’s still work?</question>
      <answer>Yes. With Overheat, orange battle icons don’t add to the attack value, but they were still flipped, so any other effects that care about flipping orange battle icons will still work. The same is true for black battle icons.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-02" id="502-1">
      <question>
My question is the following scenario:
Player A has one bot remaining with 1 health 
Player B has one bot remaining with 3 health
Player A attacks with his one remaining bot into Player B's bot that has Energized Field equipped.
Player A's total attack value after flipping all cards (attack and defense flips) is enough to kill Player B's bot BUT during the defense card flips Player B flips a single orange card thus triggering Energized Field’s ability.
What would be the order of operations?
      </question>
      <answer>
Energized Field’s ability would trigger before damage is dealt, KO’ing Player A’s last character and winning the game for Player B.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="32">
        <question>
            What does it mean that “my deck can have up to 1 extra STAR of cards?” Does that mean characters or battle cards?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Your Battle deck may include 1 Star card and still be considered a Legal Deck. Examples include Mounted Missiles, Energized Field, Leap of Faith, etc.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="38">
        <question>
            What does it mean that “my deck can have up to 1 extra STAR of cards?” Does that mean characters or battle cards?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Your Battle deck may include 1 Star card and still be considered a Legal Deck. Examples include Mounted Missiles, Energized Field, Leap of Faith, etc.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      </target></faq>