<faq><target name="Inverted!"><entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-43" tags="Inverted!,Play">
      <question>
I have run into a situation where my deck had no cards and no discard pile to shuffle in. We ruled it as when I attacked or defended, I had no cards to flip so I added 0 to my attack and defense. We were wondering if this would be a proper ruling. Second, for the card Inverted. It says that for each orange pip you flip becomes a blue pip and vice versa. For cards that rely on you flipping a certain color pip, do the pips flipped count as what they are or the inverted color?
</question>
      <answer>
When you have no deck left, you just don’t flip any cards. Inverted’s effect applies immediately. For example, if an ability triggers whenever you flip two orange icons, and you flip two blue icons under Inverted (meaning the cards literally have blue icons printed on them), that ability will trigger.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-29" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
Does Inverted! supersede other effects that look at pips? Or can the order be chosen? For example, Inverted! with Thermal Weaponry, could a blue pip add to pierce before changing into an orange pip?
      </question>
      <answer>
Battle icon colors do not exist simultaneously. When Battle Icons are made to change colors, it happens instantaneously.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-18" tags="Inverted!,Alpha Trion - Cybertronian Sage">
      <question>
How does Alpha Trion's ability interact with Inverted?
</question>
      <answer>
While equipped with inverted, an attacking Alpha Trion may play an action with an orange icon they've flipped (because it counts as a blue icon). He will not be able to play any actions with blue icons you may flip, because they count as orange. "Good job!" - The Design Team.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-08-09" id="3-19" tags="Inverted!">
      <question>
Second, for the card Inverted. It says that each orange pip you flip becomes a blue pip and vice versa. For cards that rely on you flipping a certain color pip, do the pips flipped count as what they are, or the inverted color?
</question>
      <answer>
For Inverted, there's no sequence when the icon changes from one color to another. They are changed from the moment Inverted is played and stay so as long as Inverted is on the character.
</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-9">
      <question>
What happens to Thermal Weaponry when Inverted! is in play?
      </question>
      <answer>
Then your orange battle icons would add to your pierce but not your blues.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-21">
      <question>
How does Inverted! interact with other cards and abilities which care about the color of your flipped battle icons? Are battle icons ever in a 'natural' state immediately after they've been flipped off the deck, but before Inverted! has modified them?
      </question>
      <answer>
Inverted! applies immediately. There is no in-between or “natural” state.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>