<faq><target name="Leap of Faith"><entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="85">
      <question>What happens if I play Leap of Faith with only 1 card left in my deck?</question>
      <answer>First, you’ll scrap that card. Then you’ll shuffle all the other cards in your scrap pile into your deck. Then you may play the card you scrapped. If you don’t, it will stay in your scrap pile. Then scrap the new top card of your deck and you may play it.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-10" id="510-13">
      <question>
When attacking with Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend we know you can't play Supercharge from your attack flip, but what if you play Leap of Faith and scrap Supercharge?
      </question>
      <answer>
You CAN play Supercharge off of OPBL (or via Leap of Faith), but it probably won’t do what you want it to do. It does give Bold 3, but because battle cards have already been flipped for this attack, that Bold 3 won’t do anything. But you could still play it. You know, for fun.
However, if the character you give Bold 3 to gets to attack later in the same turn, that Bold 3 will be in effect.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-06-28" id="628-11">
      <question>
Does Leap of Faith get around requirement cards (Tech Research, Ancient Wisdom) like Hunker Down does? If I flip a superior equipment, can I play that without the Tech Research?
      </question>
      <answer>
Leap of Faith gives you the ability to play a card, but that card’s requirements must still be met. 
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-4">
      <question>
Does Skywarp - Teleporting Seeker's bot mode ability trigger when playing a Secret Action from hand since the pip color is hidden information from your opponent? Will his bot mode ability trigger if it is played from the top of the deck via Leap of Faith since the pip color is no longer hidden information?
</question>
      <answer>
Yes, Skywarp's bot mode ability would be triggered by a Secret Action as the battle icon color is hidden. It will still trigger if Leap of Faith plays a Secret Action because at the time you play the Secret Action, the Secret Action has no battle icons (it's not very secret).
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-05" id="405-5">
      <question>
I have Wheeljack - Weapons Inventor in alt mode on the field. I play Leap of Faith and flip Field Communicator as my first card. I play Field Communicator and equip it to Wheeljack. With this scenario, does Wheeljack’s ability to draw then scrap a card occur before I do my second flip for Leap of Faith or does it have to wait until Leap of Faith has fully resolved?
      </question>
      <answer>
EDIT: You must resolve Leap of Faith and the second card you flip from Leap of Faith, then Field Communicator’s ability and Wheeljack’s ability can be resolved in an order of your choosing.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-22" id="222-13">
      <question>
So, with Leap of Faith: it says to scrap a card, which you may play, then scrap another card, and you may play that. For actions, it's a no brainer. But for upgrades, if you play it from your scrap, does it stay on the battlefield?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes. You’ll play the upgrade just as you would from your hand and it will remain attached to the character as normal.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-01" id="401-8" tags="Superior Cannon,Superior Jetpack,Superior Plating">
      <question>
Can Leap of Faith bypass the condition on all the Superior cards (Cannon, Jet pack, Plating) and allow you to attach them to a bot?
      </question>
      <answer>
No.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-13">
      <question>
Would like to check with you during situation of Brainstorm being used, the other 2 actions after Brainstorm are Ancient Wisdom and Leap of Faith. While flipping for Leap of Faith, I somehow manage to flip 2 Unleash Potentials. Does that mean that I get to bring back two 1-star cards outside the game I owned?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes, if you played the Ancient Wisdom first.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-14">
      <question>
Next, is there a sequencing issue with the synergy of Ancient Wisdom and Unleash Potential? Say while playing Leap of Faith, I flipped Unleash Potential first and then flipped Ancient Wisdom, do I still get to bring in a 1-star card?
      </question>
      <answer>
No, that would not do anything.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-08" id="9-1">
      <question>
Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend flips completely for his attack &amp; chooses Leap of Faith as his Action. The first card Leap of Faith reveals is Grenade Launcher. If I attach it to Optimus Prime Battlefield Legend, does he immediately get the +4 Attack boost?
        </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-11-08" id="9-2">
      <question>
Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend is equipped with Power Punch, flips completely for his attack, and chooses Leap of Faith as his Action. The first card Leap of Faith reveals is W-5 Gyro Blaster. If OPBL attaches this, do I keep all the flips revealed from Power Punch? If so, does that mean my opponent now cannot flip more than 2 cards for their defense now that W-5 Gyro Blaster has been attached?
        </question>
      <answer>
No, W-5 Gyro Blaster’s ability only triggers if it’s attached when the character attacks or defends.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="32">
        <question>
            What does it mean that “my deck can have up to 1 extra STAR of cards?” Does that mean characters or battle cards?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Your Battle deck may include 1 Star card and still be considered a Legal Deck. Examples include Mounted Missiles, Energized Field, Leap of Faith, etc.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="ATP:Alpha Trion Protocols Wave 2 FAQ" id="38">
        <question>
            What does it mean that “my deck can have up to 1 extra STAR of cards?” Does that mean characters or battle cards?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Your Battle deck may include 1 Star card and still be considered a Legal Deck. Examples include Mounted Missiles, Energized Field, Leap of Faith, etc.
        </answer>
      </entry>
      </target></faq>