<faq><target name="Press the Advantage"><entry id="3">
          <question>What Cards are banned in Constructed Tournaments?</question>
          <answer>
              The Battle Cards Swap Parts and Press the Advantage are banned from use in Constructed play. 
              The Battle Card Multi-Mission Gear has also been announced as banned.
          </answer>
      </entry>
  <entry id="88">
      <question>Can I play this if I don’t have any Autobots or my opponent doesn’t have any Decepticons just to get one of the effects?</question>
      <answer>Yes.</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="89">
      <question>Let’s say I play this and choose my opponent’s Decepticon with 1 defense. Later in the turn, it gets +2 defense. What will its total defense be?</question>
      <answer>1. Press the Advantage won’t drop the Decepticon’s defense below 0, but the -2 applies again once the Decepticon’s defense is raised.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry id="1-16">
      <question>
If I am playing a team of Decepticon characters, can I still play Press the Advantage? None of my characters would get an attack boost, but a defending Decepticon gets -2 defense?
</question>
      <answer>
Yes, you may play Press the Advantage. You don’t have an Autobot to give +2 attack to, but you can still give an enemy Decepticon -2 defense.
Note: Any Decepticons on your team will no longer be welcome at the Decepticon company barbecue after you do this.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="607-2" tags="Acid Storm - Toxic Terror">
      <question>
I attack into my opponents Acid Storm which has 0 defense. Before attacking I play Press the Advantage. My opponent flips defense cards and gets 3 defense. Does Press the Advantage bring him down to 1 defense or because it was played when he had 0 defense does he stay at 0 because the card says he can't go below 0?
      </question>
      <answer>
In this scenario, Press the Advantage would bring your opponent’s character down to 1 defense. Any attack or defense modifiers apply for their stated duration. Only when the result is less than 0 do you use 0 instead.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>