<faq><target name="Rapid Conversion"><entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-RR-1" id="RR1-8">
      <question>
Can a character in the KO area be flipped, when you choose a character to flip for the turn and/or through action cards like Rapid Conversion?
      </question>
      <answer>
You can flip for the turn, but no cards in the game can effect characters in the K.O. Area unless specifically stated.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-RR-1" id="RR1-19">
      <question>
Can Rapid Conversion be used to flip a character in the KO area? We know now that we can use our flip for the turn to do this, can cards like Rapid Conversion be used?
      </question>
      <answer>
No, cards cannot effect cards in the K.O. Area unless specifically stated.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-RR-1" id="RR1-20" tags="Thrust - Supersonic Interceptor">
      <question>
Would Thrust grant +5 to Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend if Rapid Conversion was played when using Prime’s bot mode ability.
      </question>
      <answer>
No. The amount of bonus granted by Thrust is granted at the time his ability is triggered and not modified afterwards.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-18">
      <question>
Say I attack with Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend with a Rapid Conversion in my hand and flip a Brainstorm for the attack. If I play the Brainstorm and play the Rapid Conversion from hand to target Optimus, am I able to play the action that he retrieves from the graveyard as the second action for Brainstorm?
      </question>
      <answer>
No. You must fully resolve Brainstorm before the ability from his flip triggers.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-08-09" id="3-12">
      <question>
Can you transform an already tapped character in the field? (For example .. I want to play Rapid Conversion on Barrage who is tapped). If yes, will this still trigger his ability? (He can give another character +2 Pierce when he is flipped to Bot mode.)
</question>
      <answer>
Yes and yes!
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-22" id="322-4" tags="Demolisher - Devoted Decepticon,Megatron - Decepticon Leader">
      <question>
Regarding character triggers, the following scenario is Demolisher/Darkmount/Common Megatron all in bot mode. I play Brainstorm &gt; Hunker Down &gt; Rapid Conversion. Hunker Down flips all 3 to alt mode, then I play armors from the scrap pile if able. Once Hunker Down is complete, I play Rapid Conversion targeting Megatron to flip him into bot mode. Brainstorm is now resolved. Moving on to character triggers, would Demolisher’s ability now draw 1 or 2 cards? Would I be allowed to use Megatron’s flip ability? 
      </question>
      <answer>
In this scenario, Demolisher’s ability would draw 1 card and you would be able to use Megatron’s flip ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-08" id="308-7" tags="Silverbolt - Aerialbot Leader,Thrust - Supersonic Interceptor">
      <question>
Say Silverbolt attacks and his alt-mode ability triggers, allowing him to flip to bot mode thus making his base attack 3. If that is the case, then why would Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend not get +5 attack if he attacks, uses his bot-mode ability and flips Rapid Conversion which in turn flips a tapped Thrust to bot-mode? Both Silverbolt and Thrust have triggered abilities but only Silverbolt benefits from the higher attack value. Why? Thrust’s alt-mode effect mentions “this character” NOT “this mode” or “alt mode”?
      </question>
      <answer>
Thrust’s ability only triggers at the time of attack and does not check again. Silverbolt is not adding his attack, he is using his attack to determine the damage at the last point after he’s flipped and just before damage is dealt.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-14" tags="Autobot Cosmos - Recon &amp; Communication">
      <question>
When I attack with Cosmos in bot mode and then Anticipation Engine activates and I flip Rapid Conversion and flip him to alt mode. Would his KO effect take place since he’s no longer in bot mode? And I no longer have cards in my deck?
</question>
      <answer>
If during Cosmos’ attack, Anticipation Engine reveals Rapid Conversion as the last card in your deck, and you play it, you will immediately shuffle your deck, triggering Cosmos’ ability, then flip Cosmos to Alt Mode.
</answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>