<faq><target name="Recon System"><entry id="90">
      <question>Let’s say I flip 3 battle cards (the normal 2 + 1 for Recon System) and there’s a white battle icon there. Do I scrap one for Recon System’s effect immediately or do I flip the 2 extra cards?</question>
      <answer>Flip the extra cards first, then choose one of the cards you flipped and scrap it.</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="91">
      <question>If I put Recon System on Optimus Prime, Battlefield Legend (bot mode), can I scrap an Action that I flipped and then play it?</question>
      <answer>No. By the time you use Prime’s ability to play one of the Action cards, it will be in the scrap pile and not among the cards you flipped.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry id="628-22">
      <question>
If I have Emergency Defense Field and Recon System attached to my character, and it’s attacked, can I choose which battle card to scrap (Recon System) after both player’s cards are flipped, to try and trigger Energy Defense Field? 
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes, you can choose which card to scrap. The attacker always flips first, then the defender. Since you’re defending, you’ll know what the attacker flipped when you have to decide for Recon System. 
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="218-9">
      <question>
I attack with Starscream - Decepticon King in Bot mode, who is equipped with Recon System. I flip battle cards and flip a Decepticon Crown. If I use Recon System to scrap Decepticon Crown, does Starscream still get its effect since Decepticon Crown was flipped, despite it being scrapped later?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="222-1">
      <question>
When does a white battle icon trigger during a battle? If I have Recon System equipped to a battling character and I flip a white and an orange, will Recon System trigger first or the white icon?
      </question>
      <answer>
Recon System says you scrap it without using its battle icons, and it will happen first.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="322-9">
      <question>
If I attack with Optimus Prime - Battlefield Legend, equipped with Recon System, can I select the scrapped card since it was still flipped during an attack by Optimus Prime?
      </question>
      <answer>
If you scrap an action, Optimus Prime won’t be able to find it, as it has left the played area.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="308-25">
      <question>
In the FAQ, it is stated that when a white icon is flipped, you flip the additional 2 cards, and then scrap the card for Recon System.  Is the card with the white icon an available choice to scrap, even though it was used to flip 2 additional cards?
      </question>
      <answer>
We’ve amended the answer in the FAQ to read: Choose one of the cards you flipped, scrap it, then flip the 2 extra cards.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="308-26">
      <question>
When Recon System is equipped on a character like Skywarp - Teleporting Seeker, will his ability still trigger if you scrap the only card with no icons, since you did actually flip the card, triggering Skywarp's ability?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
    </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="228-10">
      <question>
If you attack with Bombshell - Decepticon Psy Ops in bot mode and the defender has the 1-star upgrade Recon System attached, is that +1 to the total number of cards to be scrapped by the attacker? No. Bombshell’s ability only counts stars from characters, not from battle cards.

Are you allowed to look at your opponent’s discard pile?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes. The discard pile and KO zones are areas of public information. Accurate information must be provided upon request during a game, but please be polite about it, and always ask permission before touching another player’s cards and handle them carefully.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>