<faq><target name="Security Console"><entry id="315-16">
      <question>
When does Security Console trigger? Before or after my opponent flips their battle cards for their attack? 
      </question>
      <answer>
Security Console triggers before your opponent flips their battle cards.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="10-33">
      <question>
My question is about the interaction of Debilitating Crystal and the new Expanded Rules document. If my attacker has a Debilitating Crystal, and the Defender has a Gyro Blaster I wish to return, I believe the Gyro Blaster would still limit each character to 2 flips this battle. Is this correct? I know a previous Rules Roundup clarified that a Security Console would still Draw and Plan even if a Debilitating Crystal returned it. Is this also the case with a Sparring Gear I wish to return? Do they still have Tough 2 this battle?
        </question>
      <answer>
Expanded Rules point 8.5 indicates the Gyro Blaster is returned before flips are determined, so it will not affect them. Likewise, Sparring Gear will no longer grant Tough 2 when flips are determined.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="422-1">
      <question>
I was looking for clarity on when triggers occur during the window when attackers and defenders are declared. Can Debilitating Crystal bounce Security Console before it gets to trigger?
      </question>
      <answer>
Choosing the attacker and which character it’s attacking is a single step. After that, any abilities that trigger when a character attacks (but don’t refer to what’s flipped) happen, followed by any abilities of the defender. In your scenario, Debilitating Crystal would not bounce Security Console before it triggers.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="322-10" tags="Dreadwing - Sky Destroyer">
      <question>
My question revolves around Dreadwing, and if there are 2 Security Consoles equipped in the 2 Utility Slots. Would you resolve each Security Console's effects one at a time? Or would you Draw 2 Cards and then Plan 2? (As each Security Console gives lets your Draw a card then Plan 1)
      </question>
      <answer>
Multiple Security Consoles should be resolved one at a time. Their effects do not combine. If you put a card on the top of your deck from the first one, be sure to act surprised when you draw it again.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="426-6">
      <question>
Can you elaborate on today's ruling? Wouldn't Security Console no longer be in play to resolve its trigger? Or is the effect independent of the card that triggered it once the trigger occurs?
      </question>
      <answer>
Once an ability triggers, it will happen even if the card that has that ability leaves the battlefield (or other zone, if appropriate) in the meantime.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="607-18" tags="Prowl - Strategic Mastermind,Autobot Mirage - Counterintelligence">
      <question>
What happens when the Sentinel Prowl attacks with Combat Commands and I want to use it on Mirage, into a character equipped to with Security Console? Does turn player flip flop Mirage first to look for an action to scrap before they draw?
      </question>
      <answer>
The attack causes two abilities to trigger. One is yours (Combat Commands) and the other is your opponent’s (Security Console). You do yours first, but this causes another of your abilities to trigger (Mirage). You continue to use your abilities until you have none, then your opponent can use any of their pending abilities in any order. In this scenario, you would first use Combat Commands’ ability, then use Mirage’s ability, then your opponent would use Security Console’s ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>