<faq><target name="Battle Icon"><entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="5" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
             What is a Green Battle Icon?
        </question>
      <answer>
             This set introduces a new battle icon: green! Here’s how it works. After a battle in which you
flipped at least one card with a green battle icon, you may swap a card in your hand with one of
the cards you flipped with a green battle icon. The card you swap from your hand will be
scrapped at the end of the turn, along with all the other cards you played or flipped during the
turn.
        </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="6" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
             I flipped 2 cards with green battle icons. Can I return both of them to my hand by swapping
two cards?
        </question>
      <answer>
             No. Only one card with a green battle icon per battle.

        </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="7" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
             If both players flip a card with a green battle icon, who decides first?
        </question>
      <answer>
             The player whose turn it is goes first, then the other player.
        </answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="129" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
          What is a Black Battle Icon?
      </question>
      <answer>

There’s a new battle icon on some battle cards in War for Cybertron: Siege I. It’s black! What
does it mean? If you’re on the attack, hopefully good things for you.
For each black battle icon you flip while attacking, your character gets pierce 1 until end of turn.
Remember that pierce numbers add up, so flipping two black icons in an attack will give your
attacker pierce 2, and so on.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="130" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
             Do black battle icons have any effect on a character that’s defending?
        </question>
      <answer>
             No. Black battle icons flipped on defense won’t give your character pierce. (And pierce
doesn’t work on defense anyway.)
      </answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-7" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
So on Spare Parts it says after each battle you may swap 1 card from your hand with one of your flipped green pip cards, is this just a printing of the base rule, or a card effect that lets you swap out a second green pip?
      </question>
      <answer>
That’s just reminder text for anyone who may have forgotten how the green battle icons work.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-15" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
What does ‘each battle’ entail regarding green icons? For example, if my opponent has 3 attacks on my one character, every time I flip a green battle icon for each individual battle that turn, I can add one green icon for each battle, totaling 3? 
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes. You can get one green battle icon per battle.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-15" id="315-17" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
Hello. I have a question about green pips and turns with multiple attacks. When does the card exchange happen? After each attack? After all attacks are resolved? If it is after all attacks are resolved, do you only exchange for one card, or do you exchange for each attack? In the rules it used the term battle and I was not sure if that meant each attack or all attacks.
      </question>
      <answer>
You can swap for a green battle icon card after each attack has finished. If there are multiple attacks in a turn, you can swap for one green battle icon card after each of those attacks, I.E. attack, swap, attack, swap, and so on.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-29" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
Does Inverted! supersede other effects that look at pips? Or can the order be chosen? For example, Inverted! with Thermal Weaponry, could a blue pip add to pierce before changing into an orange pip?
      </question>
      <answer>
Battle icon colors do not exist simultaneously. When Battle Icons are made to change colors, it happens instantaneously.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-01" id="401-11" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question> 
The wording on what exactly goes on with green pip cards added to the hand from the flip zone has me minorly confused. 
1. When the swap occurs, is the card from hand exchanged scrapped then or at the end of the turn?
2. Does this trigger the bot mode ability of Decepticon Shockwave - Cyberton Commander?
      </question>
      <answer>
1. At the end of the battle, you can swap one card in your hand for a green battle icon card you’ve flipped.
2. It does not trigger Shockwave’s ability because you’re not scrapping a card from your hand. The flipped cards are being scrapped.
      </answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-11" id="211-14" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
Let's say that my opponent has 1 single untapped character with 2 defense. It is my turn and I have 2 or 3 characters, so I will attack multiple times. During my first attack my opponent flipped 1 or 2 blue icons. The question is: During my second attack, my opponent's character will start the battling with 2 defense or with 4 defense? Also, the same may happen with the orange icon if I got a way to attack twice with the same player in a turn?
      </question>
      <answer>
The Battle Icons you flip are only effective for that individual battle. Attack and Defense increases will not carry over.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-28" id="528-1" tags="Raider Cindersaur - Black Ops - Demolitions,Alpha Trion - Cybertronian Sage,Battle Icon">
      <question>
Alpha Trion and Raider Cindersaur label actions by the colored battle icons. Can you explain what makes a card an Orange or Blue Card? Does that mean that they have to have at least one orange icon to be an orange card? If this is the case, then can Alpha Trion use his ability to play a Roll Out! because it has at least 1 blue icon?
      </question>
      <answer>
A “blue card” is a card with at least one blue battle icon, and so on for the other colors, so you would be able to play Roll Out with Alpha Trion’s ability.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-28" id="528-2" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
Say I, on my opponent's turn, have Infiltrate facedown and they play a secret action that has an orange icon (I, of course, don't know this). How does this interaction work, considering secret actions are considered actions?
      </question>
      <answer>
Infiltrate will never affect a Secret Action because as you’ve said, you can’t see its Battle Icons as it’s played.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-28" tags="Battle Icon">
      <question>
Question about green battle icons and how the work. The text on a card with a green icon says "After a battle, you swap a card from your hand with a green icon you flipped" does this mean since Swarm makes you flip the battle cards. Can you grab a green icon you flipped for Swarm after you battle?
</question>
      <answer>
No, only cards with green battle icons that you flipped during that battle can be retrieved after the battle.
</answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>