<faq><target name="Head Mode &amp; Body Mode"><entry id="6">
            <question>
                What are Head &amp; Body modes?
            </question>
            <answer>
                Titan Masters Attack introduces two new character modes that work together: head mode and body mode.
                Cards with a head mode are placed above a character that has a body mode, combining them into a single character. The resulting character is a single character made up of both cards. The body mode card will tell you the character's stats and abilities, and the head mode card will give the character a bonus. That bonus may be an added ability or an increase to attack, defense, or health. Like other characters, that character starts the game in alt mode. If the character is KO'd, even if it's your last character card, the card with head mode is returned to the battlefield in bot mode. That bot mode character can't flip.
            </answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="7">
        
            <question>
                The character card with head mode and the one with body mode each have stars. Do those stars all count toward my deck limit?
            </question>
            <answer>
                Yes. Each card's stars count toward the 25-star limit. During the game, the character has all the stars from its two cards.
            </answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="8">
        
            <question>
                What happens if the character flips?
            </question>
            <answer>
                The body mode card can flip back and forth, from alt mode to body mode. The head mode card doesn't flip, so its bonus always applies, no matter which mode the character is in.
            </answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="9">
        
            <question>
                Can I put any head onto any body?
            </question>
            <answer>
                Yes. They're completely mix-and-match. You could even put an Autobot head onto a Decepticon body, or vice versa.
            </answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="10">
        
            <question>
                If I have a head from one faction on a body from a different faction, which faction is the resulting character.
            </question>
            <answer>
                Both. The character is both an Autobot and a Decepticon.
            </answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="11">
        
            <question>
                If I have a character that's both an Autobot and a Decepticon, does my starting team have "only Autobots"?
            </question>
            <answer>
                No. In order to qualify as "only Autobots," your starting deck can't have any characters that are another faction (even if they're also Autobots).
            </answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="12" tags="Sideboarding">
        
            <question>
                Can I put a card with head mode or body mode in my sideboard?
            </question>
            <answer>
                You can but note that each card is a separate character card. This means you could have a character card with a head mode or one with a body mode in your sideboard, but not both.
            </answer>
        </entry>
    <entry id="610-4" tags="Play,Head Mode &amp; Body Mode">
        <question>
            Can a card target something even if it won't have an effect? For example, can Unconventional Flying Object target a Body mode character?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Cards try to do as much as they can. You can play Unconventional Flying Object even if you don't have a Spaceship and it will only accomplish putting the Action into your scrap. There are a handful of Upgrades like Crushing Treads that are restricted to play on say "Put only on a Tank." – you can't play that card unless you have the specific kind of character to put it on. After you successfully put it on the right kind of character, the game won't check anymore if the upgrade is valid, so the character can flip to Bot mode, stop being a Tank, and the Upgrade will stay on.
        </answer>
    </entry>
    
    <entry id="610-5" tags="KO,Head Mode &amp; Body Mode,Decepticon Quake - Ground Assault">
        <question>
            Can you clarify timing on when heads activate in regard to finishing a trigger that caused the Body to be KO'd? Examples: Does Decepticon Quake damage his own Head when he dies? Octone killing a Body and then his bounty triggers does this kill the Head when it is played?
        </question>
        <answer>
            A head’s deploy ability is a triggered ability. When both players trigger an ability at the same time the active player’s abilities will complete before the defending player. A player may order their own simultaneous triggers how they wish. The player controlling Quake may order Quake’s damage trigger and Quake’s head’s deploy trigger such that Quake’s damage ability resolves first, and Quake’s head second. If Octone’s controller is the active player, they must use Octone’s bounty trigger before the defending player resolves their head’s deploy trigger.
            <tftcg-note>This answer is an update on the originally published answer in the Roundup</tftcg-note>
        </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="610-7" tags="Turbo Rules,Head Mode &amp; Body Mode">
        <question>
            Do you treat the Body and Head as 1 or 2 characters?
        </question>
        <answer>
            One character.
        </answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>