<faq><target name="Play"><entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="13" tags="Peace Through Tyranny">
          <question>
             What is the Extra Turn Rule?
          </question>
          <answer> 
              Players can’t take more than two turns in a row under any circumstances. Any additional turns beyond two consecutive turns are skipped and not deferred or saved for the future. 
          </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="14">
          <question>
              How do you tap a card?
          </question>
          <answer> 
              If a card is tapped, it must be clearly turned approximately 90 degrees.
          </answer>
      </entry>
      <entry source="Tournament FAQ" id="18">
          <question>
              What is Hidden Information?
          </question>
          <answer> 
Hidden information refers to information a player isn’t allowed access to, such as the faces of cards in an opponent’s hand.
Throughout the match and pregame procedures, players are responsible for keeping their cards above the level of the playing surface and for making reasonable efforts to prevent hidden information from being revealed.
However, players may choose to reveal their hands or any other hidden information available only to them, unless specifically prohibited by the rules. Players must not actively attempt to gain information hidden from them.
          </answer>
      </entry>

  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-2" tags="Play">
      <question>
Concerning “start of turn” effects timing around the drawing 1 card from the general card rules: which of the following is true:
    You Draw 1 card from general game rules, then activate Start of Turn Effects (like Omnibots’ start of turn effects playing upgrades).
    2. You activate Start of Turn Effects, then Draw 1 card from general game rules.
    3. Drawing 1 Card from general game rules counts as a Start of Turn Effect, and can be resolved in the order of the player's choosing.
</question>
      <answer>
    1.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-43" tags="Inverted!,Play">
      <question>
I have run into a situation where my deck had no cards and no discard pile to shuffle in. We ruled it as when I attacked or defended, I had no cards to flip so I added 0 to my attack and defense. We were wondering if this would be a proper ruling. Second, for the card Inverted. It says that for each orange pip you flip becomes a blue pip and vice versa. For cards that rely on you flipping a certain color pip, do the pips flipped count as what they are or the inverted color?
</question>
      <answer>
When you have no deck left, you just don’t flip any cards. Inverted’s effect applies immediately. For example, if an ability triggers whenever you flip two orange icons, and you flip two blue icons under Inverted (meaning the cards literally have blue icons printed on them), that ability will trigger.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-3" tags="Play">
      <question>
What counts as Attack Damage and what doesn't?
      </question>
      <answer>
Attack Damage is damage dealt by the attacking character as a result of an attack. Any other damage, including damage dealt during an attack because of an ability, is non-attack damage.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-13" tags="Play">
      <question>
What happens if for any reason I`m unable to reshuffle my deck in the middle of an attack
      </question>
      <answer>
Do as much as you can. If you run out of cards in your deck and scrap pile during a battle, stop flipping and resolve that attack.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-16" tags="Play">
      <question>
If I manage to draw my entire deck into my hand, is my deck in constant reshuffle? 
      </question>
      <answer>
No. You need to actually shuffle cards in to have a successful shuffle.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-34" tags="Play">
      <question>
If we play a game of sealed, that has a ton of bold shenanigans going on, and I flip my deck, shuffle up, scrap, and flip all of my new deck but am still owed more flips, am I just out of luck?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-05-28" id="528-9" tags="Play">
      <question>
If my opponent has one tapped character and I have two untapped characters and I start my turn. I draw a card, flip a character for the turn and play an upgrade but no action. I attack with my first character. Since it is still my turn and I can attack one more time, can I play my one action for the turn for the second attack rather than the first if the scenario is more favorable? Or do all sequence events have to be done before all attacks? 
      </question>
      <answer>
Attacking is the last thing you do in your turn. So, if you want to play an action, you must do so before your first attack.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-6" tags="Play">
      <question>
Can you scrap cards from your hand? This came up from playing a lot of the Turbo format with my kids. Inevitably someone had one or two cards that you couldn't play with the characters. If you're allowed to scrap them from your hand when drawn it would still allow those cards to be useful for the pips when battling.
</question>
      <answer>
You cannot scrap cards from your hand for no reason or simply because you'd like to, but there are a plethora of effects in the game (such as green battle icons) that allow you to swap cards in and out of your hand.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-26" id="426-2" tags="Play">
      <question>
If my opponent has all tapped enemies and I have 3 untapped enemies, do I start my regular turn drawing my card, flipping one character, playing one action and upgrade, then attack with all 3 of my character one after another skipping the opponents turns until all of my characters are tapped? Or after each attack I make is my opponent allowed to draw a card, flip, and play an action and upgrade?
      </question>
      <answer>
All three attacks happen during the same turn. After your turn is done, then your opponent’s turn begins.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-26" id="426-5" tags="Play">
      <question>
Do the abilities that last "until end of turn" last until the end of your attack or until all cards untap?
      </question>
      <answer>
Neither! They last until the end of your turn. Usually, the attack is the last thing to happen during a turn, but this isn’t always true. As abilities can trigger both after the attack and at the end of turn and untapping.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-05" id="405-2" tags="Play">
      <question>
If you run out of cards in a deck, do you shuffle immediately or wait until you have to draw/flip? 
      </question>
      <answer>
Reshuffle immediately.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-05" id="405-7" tags="Play">
      <question>
Scenario: You've just reshuffled your scrap pile, you have a very large hand, and you go into battle with a lot of bold. You run out of cards in your deck to flip, and there are no cards in your scrap pile. What happens?
      </question>
      <answer>
You stop flipping and immediately regret holding onto so many cards.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-06-28" id="628-1" tags="Play,Wheeljack - Weapons Inventor">
      <question>
If you have no cards in your scrap pile and play a weapon to replace an already existing weapon on a character, does the replaced weapon immediately go to your scrap pile, or does it hit the scrap pile at the end of your turn? Asking because of Wheeljack's bot mode ability requiring a weapon in the scrap pile to give him the bold 3 effect.
      </question>
      <answer>
Immediately.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-06-28" id="628-2" tags="Play">
      <question>
Are cards flipped during battle the only ones that don't hit the Scrap Pile until the end of a turn?
      </question>
      <answer>
Actions that are played (including Secret Actions), cards you flipped during battle, and other cards you flip due to cards like Swarm!, for example, are all scrapped at the end of turn.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-06-28" id="628-23" tags="Play">
      <question>
If a card says reveal does it come into play or go back to the top. Example if I have Anticipation Engine and I reveal an upgrade does it stay in the play area until the end of turn, or go to the top of deck?
      </question>
      <answer>
Just revealing a card doesn’t cause it to move.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-12" id="412-1" tags="Play">
      <question>
When determining who goes first, does whoever wins the method used get to choose who goes first or do they HAVE to go first?
      </question>
      <answer>
For casual games, especially with newer players, we recommend the person randomly chosen goes first. For more serious, competitive games, that player can choose to go first or second.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-12" id="412-2" tags="Play">
      <question>
The Round Up two weeks ago mentioned that the loser of game 1 picks who goes first for game 2, and so on for game 3. However, the official and most recent FAQ that’s published says that the player who starts the game alternates. Which should we go by, officially, for the tiebreaker?
      </question>
      <answer>
The player who goes first alternating is meant for casual play. In a multi-game structure or best two-out-of-three scenario, the loser of one game chooses who goes first in the next game.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-12" id="412-9" tags="Play">
      <question>
It is my turn; my opponent is tapped out. I have one untapped Bot, I play Inferno Breath and tap my bot to deal 3 damage. It is now my turn to attack, but I have no bots to attack. I figure we will both untap, but who goes next? Do I attack as I have not attacked for my turn? Is it my opponent’s turn even, though I did not attack? Rules state you must attack each turn.
      </question>
      <answer>
If you have no untapped characters when it’s time to attack, you simply skip the attack and your turn ends. In the scenario you described, all characters will untap and your opponent’s turn will begin.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-12" id="412-10" tags="Play">
      <question>
When you play an action, is it set aside until the turn ends because I've seen people do that? Or when you play an action, is it set aside until it fully concludes its skill?
      </question>
      <answer>
All actions (and cards you flip for the battle) go into the played area until the end of the turn, when they are scrapped. (Secret Actions may stay in the played area a little longer).
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-12" id="412-13" tags="Play">
      <question>
Say I have 2 untapped bots and my opponent's bots are all tapped out. I do my first attack and flip. Do those cards go to the scrap pile after damage is done?
      </question>
      <answer>
They go to the scrap pile at the end of your turn.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-03-22" id="322-3" tags="Play">
      <question>
To scrap an upgrade from my own character, would I need a new upgrade in my hand, or can I just scrap it without a replacement upgrade?
      </question>
      <answer>
You need a new upgrade to replace a scrapped upgrade. Your robots like their weapons and don’t cotton to giving them up willingly.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-04-01" id="401-10" tags="Play">
      <question>
When playing Best 2 out of 3, how do you decide who goes first after the first match?
      </question>
      <answer>
There aren’t official rules for this, but we recommended letting the loser of the first game choosing who goes first in the next game.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-RR-1" id="RR1-12" tags="Play">
      <question>
Must I attack every turn?
      </question>
      <answer>
You must attack if you are able.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-RR-1" id="RR1-13" tags="Play">
      <question>
Must I flip a character every turn?
      </question>
      <answer>
No. It’s your choice whether or not to flip a character.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-RR-1" id="RR1-15" tags="Play">
      <question>
The rulebook says "When your turn ends, put all battle cards you flipped for attacks during that turn into your scrap pile. Also put any Actions you played that turn into your scrap pile." When do you scrap the cards the defender flipped for attacks?
      </question>
      <answer>
At the same time.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-RR-1" id="RR1-17" tags="Play,Jetfire - Air Guardian,Wheeljack - Weapons Inventor">
      <question>
Am I allowed to count the cards remaining in my deck (Obviously without looking at them face up)? Am I allowed to look through my scrap pile at any time, or only when prompted from a card? (e.g. Wheeljack or Jetfire)
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes and yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-11" id="211-10" tags="Play,Deck">
      <question>
Can you play action cards in your opponents turn when you’re responding to their attack and secondly can you have as many battle cards in your deck as you want, as long as it’s a minimum of 40?
      </question>
      <answer>
No, you may only play Actions if you have an Action play which is generally during your turn before you attack. You can have as many battle cards as you want over 40 as long as you can reasonably manage them.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2020-06-10" id="610-4" tags="Play,Head Mode &amp; Body Mode">
        <question>
            Can a card target something even if it won't have an effect? For example, can Unconventional Flying Object target a Body mode character?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Cards try to do as much as they can. You can play Unconventional Flying Object even if you don't have a Spaceship and it will only accomplish putting the Action into your scrap. There are a handful of Upgrades like Crushing Treads that are restricted to play on say "Put only on a Tank." – you can't play that card unless you have the specific kind of character to put it on. After you successfully put it on the right kind of character, the game won't check anymore if the upgrade is valid, so the character can flip to Bot mode, stop being a Tank, and the Upgrade will stay on.
        </answer>
    </entry>
    
    </target></faq>