<faq><target name="Triple Changer"><entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="3">
      <question>
             What are Triple Changers?
        </question>
      <answer>
             Triple Changers are characters with three modes: bot mode and two alt modes (labeled 1 and
2). They start in alt mode 1. When a Triple Changer flips, it can flip to either of the two other
modes.
        </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Wave 2 and 3 FAQ" id="4">
      <question>
             If a card specifically says to flip a Triple Changer to alt mode, what happens?
        </question>
      <answer>
             If it’s in bot mode, you can flip it to alt mode 1 or alt mode 2. If it’s in one of its alt modes,
you can either not flip it or flip it to the other alt mode.
        </answer>
    </entry>
  <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-10-25" id="8-7">
      <question>
Can Escape Route be used on a triple changer in Alt 2 to flip into Alt 1 and vice-versa? Are triple changers affected by Roll-Out if they are not in bot mode?
        </question>
      <answer>
Escape Route and Roll Out! convert characters from Bot mode to Alt mode. They cannot convert Triple Changers from one Alt mode to another Alt mode.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-4" tags="Triple Changer">
      <question>
Do Triple Changers start the game in a specific Alt Mode or do you get to choose which of the two you start in?
      </question>
      <answer>
They start in Alt Mode 1.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-02-18" id="218-7">
      <question>
If I play Cornered! on an opponent's Triple Changer, do they get to decide which Alt Mode it converts to?
      </question>
      <answer>
Yes.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-8">
      <question>
If I attack with a character that is equipped with Battering Ram and deal damage to a Triple Changer, does my opponent get to choose the mode they change to or do they have to change from Alt 1 to character and vice versa.
</question>
      <answer>
Your opponent can choose which mode of its other modes to flip to.
</answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>