<faq><target name="Backup Bag"><entry id="169">
      <question>Can I use Backup Bag to save a Weapon or Armor that causes itself to be scrapped, such as Grenade Launcher?</question>
      <answer>Yes.</answer>
    </entry>
  <entry id="7-8">
      <question>
Dreadwing is equipped with Forcefield, Emergency Defense Field, and Backup Bag takes 5 or more attack damage, what happens? I think that the Forcefield would try to scrap first (reducing the damage to 4) and the Back-Up Bag would save it... then the Emergency Defense Field would make Dreadwing take no damage and scrap. Is that right?
        </question>
      <answer>
That is correct!
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="10-28">
      <question>
Question regarding interaction between Backup Bag and weapons which can be scrapped during attack (e.g. Sturdy Javelin and Multi-Missile Pod). If I choose to scrap the weapon and it's saved by Backup Bag, can I choose to scrap it again during the same attack?
        </question>
      <answer>
No. It scraps as a result of a triggered ability, which does not trigger again. You would have to somehow attack a second time.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="628-15">
      <question>
If I play a Device Virus and select one of my armors to scrap but I have Backup Bag on that character and it scraps instead, would my opponent have to scrap armors or utilities?
      </question>
      <answer>
Your opponent would have to scrap the type of upgrade you chose with Device Virus.  
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="1-27">
      <question>
Question regarding Backup Bag + Grenade Launcher / Power Punch / RR Disruptor Blade Can I scrap backup bag instead of a weapon?
</question>
      <answer>
Yes!
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="528-6">
      <question>
Say I attack using a character equipped with Backup Bag and Grenade Launcher. After the attack, would Grenade Launcher get scrapped or would Backup Bag prevent that?
      </question>
      <answer>
Backup Bag would be scrapped in place of Grenade Launcher in this scenario.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="528-7">
      <question>
If your character takes 10 damage while it has a Force Field and a Backup Bag, will the Backup Bag save the Force Field from being scrapped while also reducing the damage down to 4?
      </question>
      <answer>
It is Force Field’s own ability that is causing it to be scrapped, so Backup Back will apply. The character will take 4 attack damage and lose the Backup Bag.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry id="2-18">
      <question>
Say I have a weapon on a character and Backup Bag as well. For my turn I placed a different or same weapon on the same character. But because I already have a weapon taken up does the original weapon get scrapped or can I keep both weapons and scrap Backup Bag instead?
</question>
      <answer>
Playing the new weapon causes the old weapon to be scrapped, but it’s the rules of the game that are doing this, not an effect of the new weapon. Backup Bag affects only cards such as Salvage for Parts or Grenade Launcher.
</answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>