<faq><target name="Recover Cassette"><entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-09-20" id="6-5">
      <question>
If a Mini-Cassette attacks with an Anticipation Engine attached, reveals Recover Cassette, and Recover Cassette is played to put that Mini-Cassette under Soundwave or Blaster, does the attack end and no cards are flipped for attacking and defending?
        </question>
      <answer>
The attack ends and no Battle Cards are flipped.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-10-11" id="7-3">
      <question>
In a turn where I play Brainstorm, allowing for 2 more actions. I play I Still Function!, bringing Buzzsaw (Spy) from the KO Area, then I play Recover Cassette, putting Buzzsaw underneath Soundwave. Will that cancel out I Still Function!?
        </question>
      <answer>
Yes, it will. Once Buzzsaw goes underneath Soundwave, all existing and/or pending game effects stop applying to him.
      </answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-12" id="1-29" tags="Recover Cassette,Blaster - Communications,Soundwave - Communications">
      <question>
When you "put a cassette from the battlefield under it" does the mini-cassette heal to full or keep its damage/upgrades?
</question>
      <answer>
All of the damage is removed, and the cassette is essentially healed to full. All upgrades attached to the cassette when it's moved under its deployer are scrapped.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-08-09" id="3-2">
      <question>
How do Soundwave and Blaster decide who gets to start with the Mini-Cassette under them, for both start of game and Recover Cassette?
</question>
      <answer>
You choose where the Mini-Cassette goes.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-4">
      <question>
If I use Recover Cassette to put a Mini-Cassette under Major Soundwave, what happens to the Mini-Cassette when Major Soundwave is KO’d?
</question>
      <answer>
It stays under Major Soundwave.
</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry source="Rules Roundup 2019-07-29" id="2-29" tags="Blaster - Communications,Soundwave - Communications,I Still Function!">
      <question>
Blaster vs. Soundwave. Ravage is in the KO area. Step #1, I play brainstorm. Step #2, I play I Still Function, which brings him back with 1 health. Step #3, I play Recover Cassette, which puts him under Soundwave to heal 2 damage. Now for the question: does I Still Function resolve and Ravage goes back into the KO area? Or does Ravage bypass that effect, thus he is not KO’d?
</question>
      <answer>
Ravage is not KO’d. I Still Function does not find him on the battlefield.
</answer>
    </entry>
    </target></faq>